<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<eveapi version="2">
  <currentTime>2013-10-02 11:05:28</currentTime>
  <result>
    <rowset name="messages" key="messageID" columns="messageID">
      <row messageID="331199528"><![CDATA[Just wondering if you would mind making your characters in fleet-up.com public to the group?<br><br>The only reason I ask is that if we make our toons public to the group, we can see which toons can fly what ships in the various doctrines, which might make things easier in the long run. To enable that functionality, the creator/owner of the group needs to have public toons.<br><br>I know you usually aren't very happy to share toon skills etc, so if you would rather not, would you mind if we investigated switching ownership of the group (assuming that is even possible).<br><br>All of this is working off the assumption that you think this is a good feature, but it sounds like it could be very useful to create a fit and see exactly who can fly what.]]></row>
      <row messageID="331164757"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Hey guys, Father Sidi has some news to share with you!<br><br>I'm happy to tell you that round 2 with </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:16159//99001258">La Division Bleue</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> is happening! Oct 26, 27, 28, we will once again be squeezing a fight out of the frech. I will be orginizing this with our friends Blacksoul and Blue Fire. It will be much of the same, harass in the weeks before and Oct 26 we shoot as many POCO's as possible. I know it's boring, but the fun comes in the next 2 days. I fully expect LDB to bring a fight and fully intend to stomp them till they get QNL to help out. Please attend as it will be a blast and hopefully we can get around to blapping a few pocos. This is BOB's will.<br><br>With being jumped the other night and losing Dave's Archon, the corp has covered half of the loss. Going forward we will be creating an Corp Insurance Fund, we have a good idea about how to do this and we are finalizing the details before we present it in full. The plan at the start will be to cover our site running ships and slowly expand it into PVP fleets. Next time someone comes knocking I want to be able to go balls to the wall at them and not have to worry.<br><br>Also a reminder that if you live in Darkness Tower to start moving ships to P. Nest or Stripper. We are due for a HS hole and I don't want anyone complaining about missing ships or loot when the time comes. Also the divisions will soon be changing on the CHA's so if you have shiny loot you want no one to touchy, please get it moved into the Personal CHA. You have been warned (who's even still reading?)<br><br>Lastly I will be starting to take Applications on my FC Team. To streamline combat ops and our proficancy in combat we will have a dedicated team of FC's (hilarious title incoming) who's job it is to step up! So if you feel you have what it takes to command the BOB's army, please send me an eve mail with an app and why you should be on said team. Once I have an FC team is place I will also be creating a Doctirine Team, or DC Team.<br><br>More on that one later though. This is all Father Sidi wishes to tell you. May BOB bless us all and fly reckless!<br><br>-Sidi-</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="331199276"><![CDATA[For the tournament I would like to stream both the client and the comms, what's the best way to do that?<br><br>I think I used Xsplit last time, but I'm not wedded to it if you have a better alternative?]]></row>
      <row messageID="331163675"><![CDATA[Stupid web email truncated the last mail, sorry peeps. I am going to have to stop using that for important mails.<br><br><br>Hey all,<br><br>Okay, first of, just a gentle reminder that entry for the Cruiser tournament closes at Downtime, Thursday Oct 3, the schedule will be posted that evening. I only have two entries at the moment, so please don't procrastinate if you want to enter. Also, this is the way you enter it, just telling me on comms "Yeah I'm in" does NOT count. :)<br><br>Also, to our newer members, don't be shy in taking part, it is a lot of fun.<br><br>To enter, send an evemail to Gynax with the following format.<br><br>Subject: CRUISER TOURNAMENT - &lt;Toon Name&gt;<br><br>I will try to be accomodating on the scheduling, but no promises. :)<br><br>Like last time, if you want to switch out your toon, that will be allowed up to the start of the tournament, but don't take the piss with this, it is challenging enough to organise as it is.<br><br>One very important point, and I am going to be strict on this - participants will need to be in Caprica with their ships for the start of their match. There will be no waiting for people to fetch their ships from Amarr or Pimebeka or wherever. If you are up, and you don't have a ship, you will forfeit the match. No exceptions.<br><br>This is avoided by just having the ships you intend to compete with in Caprica, and ready to go.<br><br>Regarding ECM, I am restricting fits to TWO (2) ECM mods. The idea is to avoid situations where a Blackbird with lots of ECM mods is easily the best ship to bring, resulting in totally boring bullshit matches that are no fun to anyone, but I do not want to totally nerf ECM in the tournament either. ECM is a valid game mechanic, and I think a single ECM mod would be very weak, so I think 2 modules is a reasonable compromise.<br><br>If I am completely wrong about this, and two modules on a Blackbird is crazy powerful, I reserve the right to change these restrictions for the health of the tournament, but I will do so either in the next couple of days (with a few players making strong arguments for changing this) or after a full round of the bracket is complete (with every game being a boring Blackbird jamfest). Hopefully this will not be necessary. I have a feeling there are a couple of setups that will hard counter a jamming Blackbird anyway.<br><br>Bear in mind that a big part of the tournament is outwitting your opponent in choice of ship and fittings. It is not just a question of outflying them in the arena. The metagame is always an important part of EVE and this is something I want to preserve. If someone takes the time to properly bluff his/her opponent and chooses a hard-counter fit for the match and steamrolls it, I think that is excellent, even if the match itself is not. :)<br><br>As always, all comments and suggestions are welcome.]]></row>
      <row messageID="331146952"><![CDATA[Running with an idea of Connall's from last week, and because we have gained a few EUTZ guys over the last few weeks, I am going to do a Destroyer roam tomorrow, leaving Pimebeka/Amarr at 1900 Evetime tomorrow.<br><br>Nothing too serious, Destroyers (and maybe me in Logi frigate, depending) heading for lowsec and trying to kill stuff, and probably dying in a fire of glorious hotdropped death.<br><br>We do not need very many pilots, and non-EUTZ are welcome, so if it sounds interesting, just get on comms a bit early and we will roll out.]]></row>
      <row messageID="331234365"><![CDATA[Just a quick update.<br><br>It looks like I will have some RL stuff on till Saturday night, so the tournament will most likely be taking place on Sunday Oct 8.<br><br>Secondly, here is the current list of entrants:<br><br>Alyxxa<br>Hokosaki<br>Steve1596<br>BallisticDrone<br>Catherine Kamensky<br>Trye Askold<br>Blindwillow<br>Belle Mallissima<br><br>I shouldn't have missed anyone cos I pulled it from my mails, but let me know if you sent the mail and are not on this list. For the rest of you, it's pretty simple if you want in. Just send an evemail to Gynax with the following in the subject<br><br>CRUISER TOURNAMENT - &lt;Toon Name&gt;<br><br>and you are in.<br><br>It should be a lot of fun, T1 cruisers only, no faction or pirate ships. T1 rigs, and nothing better than T2 modules (meta 5 maximum). A maximum of 2 (TWO) ECM modules are allowed (and that is just jamming modules, not ewar in general).]]></row>
      <row messageID="330974444"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff"></font><font size="14" color="#bfffffff">Greetings Corpies,<br><br>Nominations for the new Directors are now closed.   The first round of voting will begin.  Your choices for the next CEO are as follows:<br><br></font><font size="14" color="#ff0000ff"><b><u>Nominees for Western Hemishpere (WH) Director:</u><br><br></font><font size="14" color="#ffffa600"><loc><a href="showinfo:1376//1328149095">Tandail</a><br><a href="showinfo:1383//90003608">Varos Kang</a><br><a href="showinfo:1379//92701102">Blindwillow</a><a href="showinfo:1383//90003608"> </a></loc><br><br><br></font><font size="14" color="#ff0000ff"><u>Nominee for Eastern Hemisphere (EH) Director:</u><br><br></font><font size="14" color="#ffffa600"><loc><a href="showinfo:1377//90192277">Gynax Gallenor</a></loc></b><br><br></font><font size="14" color="#bfffffff">If I have missed anyone please notify me immediately and I will correct this email.<br><br>The </font><font size="14" color="#ffff0000"><b>polls are open following the receipt of this email, and will remain open for circa 10 Days, until 00:00 Eve Time on Sunday 6 October 2013.</b>  </font><font size="14" color="#ffffffff">Based on the turnout and pace of voting last time, this is an appropriate amount of thime.<br><br></font><font size="14" color="#bfffffff">Procedures are simple, like last time...<br><br></font><font size="14" color="#ffff0000"><b>Every real person gets one vote,</b></font><font size="14" color="#bfffffff"> that can be cast with whatever toon he or she chooses.  If I have a question as to whether a real person has been represented twice, I will raise it with the candidates. </font><font size="14" color="#ff00ff00"> If anyone gets caught cheating, they will take Zep's place since the cell in Tandail's basement is free since Zep escaped....<br><br></font><font size="14" color="#bfffffff">Voting is by secret ballot (known only to me) and is simple.<br><br>Please send me an EVE Mail with</font><font size="14" color="#ff00ff00"> "OFFICIAL BALLOT for </font><font size="14" color="#ffff00ff">(insert candidate's name for WH Director AND insert candidate's name for EH DIrector</font><font size="14" color="#ff00ff00">)"</font><font size="14" color="#bfffffff"> </font><font size="14" color="#ffffff00"><b>in the subject line.<br><br>example:  "SUBJECT: OFFICIAL BALLOT for Bob The WH GOD for WH Director and Bobby the WH Devil for EH Director"<br><br></font><font size="14" color="#ff007f00"><u>That is correct there need not be any text in the EVE Mail.</b></u><br><br></font><font size="14" color="#bfffffff">At the closing of the polls I will tally the number of votes.  Winner will be determined by simple plurality (greatest number) of votes cast.<br> <br>In case of a tie..., well shit, we'll deal with that if it happens cause it shouldn't be mathematically possible.  I do not foresee a reason to go to round two short of a tie, unless we want the next WH Director to be elected with a majority of votes.  If that is the case, then we will have a run-off election with the top two vote-getters from round one.<br><br></font><font size="14" color="#ffff00ff"><i>Ain't democracy grand...</i><br><br></font><font size="14" color="#bfffffff">Good luck to all those that have been nominated.<br><br></font><font size="14" color="#ff0000ff"><b><i>Fly like you want it....</b></i><br></font><font size="14" color="#bfffffff">Kai-Lo/Jade</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="331045699"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Good day fellow pilots!<br><br>in 19 hours, at 23:30 EVE, we will be running a special armor incursion fleet. We will be forming up in </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:5//30002187">Amarr</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> for ease of refitting, as this will be one of the first armor fleets WTM has attempted. Some sample fits are available below:<br><br>Minmatar:<br></font><font size="12" color="#fff7931e"><a href="fitting:29990:2048;1:20353;1:31360;1:17559;3:30159;1:30066;1:31059;2:30110;1:13974;1:29975;1:14072;1:2969;6:13978;1:12058;1:15806;1:30133;1:2488;5:23707;5::">Loki DDD Arty</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> <br></font><font size="12" color="#fff7931e"><a href="fitting:639:2048;1:20353;1:1952;1:448;1:25894;3:519;1:18801;1:18803;1:12084;1:18807;1:1978;2:16479;2:2929;6:2488;5:23705;5::">Tempest DPS</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> <br></font><font size="12" color="#fff7931e"><a href="fitting:17732:2048;1:11648;1:1952;1:448;1:25894;3:519;2:2929;6:20353;1:5945;1:1978;2:11644;1:11646;1:16479;2:2488;5:23705;5::">Tempest Fleet Issue DPS</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> <br></font><font size="12" color="#fff7931e"><a href="fitting:17732:2048;1:11648;1:1952;1:25894;3:20353;1:519;1:1355;1:2961;6:19806;1:5945;1:1978;2:11644;1:11646;1:16479;2:2488;5:23705;5::">Tempest Fleet Issue Sniper</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> <br><br>Gallente:<br></font><font size="12" color="#fff7931e"><a href="fitting:29988:2048;1:11269;1:30056;1:3082;6:31546;1:13970;1:10190;2:31055;2:30128;1:30098;1:15891;1:29981;1:15893;1:13974;1:12058;1:11325;1:30149;1:2488;5:23707;5::">Proteus Rails</a><br><a href="fitting:641:2048;1:20353;1:1952;1:11269;1:25894;3:10190;2:18801;1:3186;7:12084;1:18837;1:18807;1:1978;1:3578;1:2488;5:23707;5::">Megathron DPS</a><a href="fitting:29988:2048;1:11269;1:30056;1:3082;6:31546;1:13970;1:10190;2:31055;2:30128;1:30098;1:15891;1:29981;1:15893;1:13974;1:12058;1:11325;1:30149;1:2488;5:23707;5::"> </a><br><a href="fitting:641:2048;1:20353;1:1952;1:12356;7:11269;1:25894;3:10190;2:18835;1:12084;1:18839;1:1978;1:3578;1:18847;1:2456;5:2488;5:23707;5::">Megathron Sniper</a><a href="fitting:29988:2048;1:11269;1:30056;1:3082;6:31546;1:13970;1:10190;2:31055;2:30128;1:30098;1:15891;1:29981;1:15893;1:13974;1:12058;1:11325;1:30149;1:2488;5:23707;5::"> </a><br><a href="fitting:17728:2048;1:20353;1:1952;1:11269;1:25894;3:10190;2:3186;7:18835;1:12084;1:18839;1:1978;1:16479;1:3578;1:18847;1:2446;5:2488;5:23707;5::">Megathron Navy Issue DPS</a><a href="fitting:29988:2048;1:11269;1:30056;1:3082;6:31546;1:13970;1:10190;2:31055;2:30128;1:30098;1:15891;1:29981;1:15893;1:13974;1:12058;1:11325;1:30149;1:2488;5:23707;5::"> </a><br><a href="fitting:17728:2048;1:20353;1:1952;1:25894;3:10190;2:3090;7:18835;1:12084;1:18839;1:14072;1:1978;1:3578;1:18847;1:2488;5:23707;5:28211;5::">Megathron Navy Issue Sniper</a><a href="fitting:29988:2048;1:11269;1:30056;1:3082;6:31546;1:13970;1:10190;2:31055;2:30128;1:30098;1:15891;1:29981;1:15893;1:13974;1:12058;1:11325;1:30149;1:2488;5:23707;5::"> </a><br><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Amarr:<br></font><font size="12" color="#fff7931e"><a href="fitting:29986:2048;1:20353;1:31462;1:30119;1:3520;6:29966;1:31055;2:448;1:30038;1:14072;1:30169;1:12058;1:18843;1:2364;1:1978;2:30078;1:18847;1::">Legion Pulses</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> <br></font><font size="12" color="#fff7931e"><a href="fitting:24692:20353;1:25894;1:26378;2:5839;1:3057;8:18835;1:12084;1:18839;1:14072;1:1978;2:5051;1:2364;1:18847;1:2488;5:23705;5::">Abaddon DPS</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> <br></font><font size="12" color="#fff7931e"><a href="fitting:17726:20353;1:25894;1:26378;2:5839;1:3057;8:18835;1:12084;1:18839;1:14072;1:1978;1:5051;1:2364;2:6173;1:18847;1:2488;5:23705;5::">Apocalypse DPS</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> <br><br>Logistics:<br></font><font size="12" color="#fff7931e"><a href="fitting:11987:31366;2:16455;4:20218;1:16487;2:5839;1:18835;1:12058;1:18843;1:11325;1:18847;1:23707;5::">Guardian Logi 4-2</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> <br></font><font size="12" color="#fff7931e"><a href="fitting:11989:2048;1:20353;1:26914;1:11269;1:31366;1:16455;3:20236;1:2032;2:31378;1:18839;1:12058;1:18843;1:2456;5:23707;5::">Oneiros Logi lv5</a><br><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">We hope to see you all there. It'll be an interesting experience for us all. As always, if you have questions please ask away.<br><br></font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><loc><a href="showinfo:1375//91586565">Sparta93</a></loc></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">, </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><loc><a href="showinfo:1376//898413254">Gantrithor105</a></loc></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">, </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><loc><a href="showinfo:1378//421457970">MrWacko</a></loc><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">WTM Leadership</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="331146753"><![CDATA[<br>Hey all,<br><br>Okay, first of, just a gentle reminder that entry for the Cruiser tournament closes at downtime, Thursday Oct 3, the schedule will be posted that evening. I only have two entries at the moment, so please don't procrastinate if you want to enter. Also, this is the way you enter it, just telling me on comms "Yeah I'm in" does NOT count. :)<br><br>Also, to our newer members, don't be shy in taking part, it is a lot of fun.<br><br>To enter, send an evemail to Gynax with the following format.<br><br>Subject: CRUISER TOURNAMENT -]]></row>
      <row messageID="330972988"><![CDATA[Hey guys,<br><br>Want to give you guys a heads up that there is a plan to take down the Darkness Tower. We will be moving in the second X-L SMA as soon as we get a Hi-Sec connection so I want people to start moving some ships in Stripper or P. Nest. Once we have that HS I want it to be a quick transition so please start moving into a new tower.<br><br>Gynax will also be collecting Full no expiry API Keys for every character in CD. We did this before but that data has long since vanished. The collection of API keys will coinside with new programs we will be launching very soon and participation will require an API key. There will be a new "Ship Replacment" in about the next 2 weeks and I know your all excited ^_^<br><br>That is all for now folks.<br><br>Fly it like you got it!<br><br>-Sidi-]]></row>
      <row messageID="331036138"><![CDATA[My bad everyone,<br><br>I forgot an important point, there will be some restrictions on ECM in the fits. I do not have full details yet, but we want to avoid the situation where someone has a Blackbird and just jams out the other guy for the whole time cos that is not fun and tends to break these tournaments.<br><br>I am not entirely sure of how we restrict this, but it will probably be alon the lines of a maximum number of ECM modules allowed in fits. I will have full details in the next day or two.<br><br>Sorry for this, I knew I was forgetting something important.]]></row>
      <row messageID="331040336"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Just a reminder to everyone that we are always going to have fitted ships on corp contract.<br><br>I believe currently there are 2 Enyos, 1 Sacrilege and 1 Deimos available, all of them in Pimebeka.<br><br>The cost of the fitted ships is roughly the Amarr buy price (or at least what the corp spent on the ships)<br><br></font><font size="12" color="#fff7931e"><a href="contract:30001669//72708737">[Multiple Items] (Enyo)</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> <br><br></font><font size="12" color="#fff7931e"><a href="contract:30001669//72708750">[Multiple Items] (Enyo)</a><br><br><a href="contract:30001669//72798310">[Multiple Items] (Deimos)</a><a href="contract:30001669//72708750"> </a><br><br><a href="contract:30001669//72798645">[Multiple Items] (Sacrilege)</a><a href="contract:30001669//72708750"> </a><br><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">If these ships expire, I will just relist them. Our plan is to make sure line ships from our doctrines will always be available on corp contract.</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="330971931"><![CDATA[Way up north where the air gets cold <br>We're running out of money and we're running out of gold <br>So now I earn my living <br>Killing the baby seals <br><br>You can hit `em with a bat you can hit `em with a brick <br>You can poke `em in th eye with your eye pokin stick <br>That's how I earn my living <br>Killing the baby seals <br><br>You can slash `em in the head you can slash `em in the throat <br>Then throw `em in the back of your fishing boat <br>That's how I earn my living <br>Killing the baby seals. ]]></row>
      <row messageID="331006340"><![CDATA[<br>Just a couple of points about the cruiser tournament.<br><br>First, applications for the tournament is open till the morning of Thursday, Oct 3. Prior to that, I will send out an evemail with all the applicants I have listed, probably on the Wednesday. Once the entrants are finalised, I will add them all to the website and do the brackets. The brackets will determine the matchups and the start time. I will schedule matches in 10 minute intervals, though I am not sure exactly what time we will start, as we will try to accomodate as many people as possible, so this really depends on the numbers.<br><br>Second, I implied this in the email, but just to be clear, just one toon per player, but like last time, you are free to change out your toon prior to the list being finalised next week. Once the brackets are up though, the toon you entered is the one you need to use.<br><br>Thirdly, since it is Double Elimination, the minimum ships you are likely to need is two. Like before, fits do not need to be declared prior to the match starting, so if you want to have a small stable of choices, that is perfectly fine.<br><br>Fourthly, all matches will take place in Caprica, so make sure you are in the wormhole, just in case Bob frowns on us that day.<br><br>Our plan is to make tournaments like this a monthly thing, and I am open to all sorts of ideas for tournaments, so feel free to get in touch with me if you have something you like the sound of.]]></row>
      <row messageID="330928133"><![CDATA[Sorry about tonight, cooking dinner took longer than I expected.<br><br>I think the idea of fitting a catalyst and dying in a fire is a great one though, lets try to organise this again for either Tuesday or Wednesday this week. Sounds like fun.]]></row>
      <row messageID="330763069"><![CDATA[<br>Cue the punk music...<br><br>Alright, this one is short in deference to Pflepsen... if I say too much he is going to feel left out.<br><br>We are going to do a 1v1 T1 Cruiser tournament, similar set up to the frigate one that ZeP missed and is still in the basement for, desperately thinking of ways to make the Master happy.<br><br>T1 cruisers only (no Navy or Pirate stuff), T2 fits only (Meta 5 and lower), and T1 rigs only (you big cheaty-pants Angel).<br><br>I am going to be stricter on the schedule this time, and if there was be no waiting for people to run to Amarr/Jita/Wherever to buy and fit a ship.<br><br>Structure will be double elimination, and I will do signups on that site if it is easy to do so. If not, I will take applications via evemail after I have fully written up the rules like last time.<br><br>The tournament is open to all members of the corp apart from myself and Pflepsen (assuming that Pflepsen is willing to be the referee/arena again)<br><br>Date: Oct 5-6, 2013 - but will pick a time that suits as many members as possible<br>Prize: A Navy Battlecruiser Hull of the winner's choice<br><br>We may have other prizes too.<br><br>I have one little personal request too. Someone other than Oma needs to fly out of the arena this time, cos that took all the fun out of it.<br><br>I will also set up a proper stream of the tournament this time, so we don't have a load of observers on grid, it got confusing and awkward last time, and having a stream should help solve that.]]></row>
      <row messageID="330974676"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff">(Had to add a nominee....)<br><br><br></font><font size="14" color="#bfffffff">Greetings Corpies,<br><br>Nominations for the new Directors are now closed.   The first round of voting will begin.  Your choices for the next CEO are as follows:<br><br></font><font size="14" color="#ff0000ff"><b><u>Nominees for Western Hemishpere (WH) Director:</u><br><br></font><font size="14" color="#ffffa600"><loc><a href="showinfo:1376//1328149095">Tandail</a><br><a href="showinfo:1383//90003608">Varos Kang</a><br><a href="showinfo:1379//92701102">Blindwillow</a><a href="showinfo:1383//90003608"> </a><br><a href="showinfo:1376//1075598849">Pflepsen</a><a href="showinfo:1383//90003608"> </a></loc><br><br></font><font size="14" color="#ff0000ff"><u>Nominee for Eastern Hemisphere (EH) Director:</u><br><br></font><font size="14" color="#ffffa600"><loc><a href="showinfo:1377//90192277">Gynax Gallenor</a></loc></b><br><br></font><font size="14" color="#bfffffff">If I have missed anyone please notify me immediately and I will correct this email.<br><br>The </font><font size="14" color="#ffff0000"><b>polls are open following the receipt of this email, and will remain open for circa 10 Days, until 00:00 Eve Time on Sunday 6 October 2013.</b>  </font><font size="14" color="#ffffffff">Based on the turnout and pace of voting last time, this is an appropriate amount of thime.<br><br></font><font size="14" color="#bfffffff">Procedures are simple, like last time...<br><br></font><font size="14" color="#ffff0000"><b>Every real person gets one vote,</b></font><font size="14" color="#bfffffff"> that can be cast with whatever toon he or she chooses.  If I have a question as to whether a real person has been represented twice, I will raise it with the candidates. </font><font size="14" color="#ff00ff00"> If anyone gets caught cheating, they will take Zep's place since the cell in Tandail's basement is free since Zep escaped....<br><br></font><font size="14" color="#bfffffff">Voting is by secret ballot (known only to me) and is simple.<br><br>Please send me an EVE Mail with</font><font size="14" color="#ff00ff00"> "OFFICIAL BALLOT for </font><font size="14" color="#ffff00ff">(insert candidate's name for WH Director AND insert candidate's name for EH DIrector</font><font size="14" color="#ff00ff00">)"</font><font size="14" color="#bfffffff"> </font><font size="14" color="#ffffff00"><b>in the subject line.<br><br>example:  "SUBJECT: OFFICIAL BALLOT for Bob The WH GOD for WH Director and Bobby the WH Devil for EH Director"<br><br></font><font size="14" color="#ff007f00"><u>That is correct there need not be any text in the EVE Mail.</b></u><br><br></font><font size="14" color="#bfffffff">At the closing of the polls I will tally the number of votes.  Winner will be determined by simple plurality (greatest number) of votes cast.<br> <br>In case of a tie..., well shit, we'll deal with that if it happens cause it shouldn't be mathematically possible.  I do not foresee a reason to go to round two short of a tie, unless we want the next WH Director to be elected with a majority of votes.  If that is the case, then we will have a run-off election with the top two vote-getters from round one.<br><br></font><font size="14" color="#ffff00ff"><i>Ain't democracy grand...</i><br><br></font><font size="14" color="#bfffffff">Good luck to all those that have been nominated.<br><br></font><font size="14" color="#ff0000ff"><b><i>Fly like you want it....</b></i><br></font><font size="14" color="#bfffffff">Kai-Lo/Jade</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="330902123"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Good day fellow incursioners! Warp To Me SRP is now offering extended coverage to any who purchase it. For a limited time you can be covered by the Warp To Me SRP for up to 4 billion isk. Extended coverage costs 30m, and covers you from downtime to downtime, just like standard coverage.<br><br>When purchasing SRP coverage, you must deposit the exact amount for the coverage you wish. You cannot upgrade from 10m/2B coverage to 30m/4B without depositing the full 30 million isk into the Warp To Me SRP corporation. All other rules regarding SRP coverage apply. Depending on results, we will tweak and continue expanded coverage as needed.<br><br>If you have any questions regarding expanded coverage, Warp to Me Leadership would be happy help.<br><br>Sincerely,<br></font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><loc><a href="showinfo:1376//898413254">Gantrithor105</a></loc></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">, </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><loc><a href="showinfo:1375//91586565">Sparta93</a></loc></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">, </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><loc><a href="showinfo:1378//421457970">MrWacko</a></loc><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">WTM Leadership<br><br>P.S. As a reminder, due to legal concerns streaming or recording WTM comms is strictly prohibited.</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="330631228"><![CDATA[Okay, so Bob said no tonight, but no worries, keep your ships good to go, the current plan is to try again in two week's time.<br><br>This should also have the side benefit that it should allow us to bring in the Sativa guys as well, so we might have quite a decent sized fleet next time.]]></row>
      <row messageID="330973130"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff"><br>Sign up for the tournament is now open and is done by sending an evemail to Gynax. The format is very simple, in the subject line needs to be of the format<br><br>Subject: CRUISER TOURNAMENT - &lt;Entrant Toon Name&gt;<br><br>And just so I can call it in advance, any muppet who non-ironically puts that verbatim into the evemail is hereby being notified to prepare for public mocking. I know there is one of you out there. :)<br><br><br><br>Tournament Rules<br><br>(Note: In the following rules, the term 'happy panda' is short-hand for the obvious cocktail of 1 Pflepsen, 1 Archon, 10 max-damage sentry drones and 1 poor unfortunate. In deference to our members' imaginations, I will omit the fine details)<br><br><br>1. Each match consist of two contestants, who are flying in T1 cruisers of any race. Navy and Pirate cruisers are not allowed.<br><br>2. Fittings must be Tech 2 or less (Meta level 5). Only T1 rigs are allowed. Anything higher than that is illegal and the contestant will be Happy Panda'd.<br><br>3. The match arena will consist of sphere within 100km of the anchor for the tournament. The anchor will be announced in advance of the match, and will be responsible for enforcing the 'Edge of Glory'. The penalty is the Happy Panda.<br><br>4. One minute before the start of the match, contestants must warp to within 30km of the anchor, who will lock them. Contestants can warp in at any they choose, from any starting point they choose. Any contestants not ready with a ship will forfeit the match.<br><br>5. Each match will last until one of the contestants is destroyed. After five minutes, the arena size will shrink by 5km every 30 seconds, shrinking to 95km from the anchor once match time goes to 5:30, 90km at 6:00 and so on till one of the contestants is destroyed.<br><br>6. The tournament structure is Double Elimination, and the brackets will be determined randomly (apart from ZePenguin and Tandail in Round 1). A match schedule will be posted in advance, but there is the possibility of rearranging games if all parties involved can agree.<br><br>7. Two minutes prior to the match, each contestant must send their fitting to the match referee. This locks your choice of ship and fit for that match, and any deviation from this will result in forfeiture of the match upon arrival in the arena. In a shock twist, the penalty is the Happy Panda<br><br>8. A website for the tournament has been created, and can be viewed at the following URL:<br><br></font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><loc><a href="http://challonge.com/cd201310cruiser">http://challonge.com/cd201310cruise</loc>r</a><br><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Once I have everyone signed up, I will put the brackets up there.<br><br>9. Only the arena anchor, match referee and two contestants are allowed on grid for matches. A stream of the game will be set up, so on-grid observation is not required. It is confusing for the contestants to have so many people on grid. Happy Panda enforcement applies.<br><br>10. The following prizes will be awarded for the tournament (one prize per pilot):<br><br>-- Overall Winner: Navy battlecruiser hull of the winner's choice<br>-- Most Entertaining/Creative Fit (as determined by the Corp Directors): T1 Battlecruiser Hull<br>-- Best-placed Pilot to not use T2 modules of any kind: Set of Genolution Core Implants</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="330641953"><![CDATA[Hey guys,<br><br>     Just wanted to say thank you for voting and thank you for your votes. Thank you to Varos for warming up the seat and pre hearding the cats. I'm honored that you have choosen me for CEO and excited to lead.<br><br>I'm not going to make any drastic or sudden changes until after the director elections and have a chance to talk to them.<br><br>One thing that I am stopping dead in its tracks however is the ship reimbursment program. That's not say it won't be back, more than likely just in another form. In its current state is a heavy tax on the corp. The rules surrounding it have been unclear, so I am pulling the plug.<br><br>I hope I can live up to the title, may BOB have mercy on our souls. Hope I earn those votes.<br><br>-Sidi-]]></row>
      <row messageID="330591815"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff"><br></font><font size="12" color="#ffb2b2b2">Greetings fellow corp mates:<br><br>Round one of CD [Y790]'s Second Election was complete as of 0000 15SEP13 UT.  Following below are the results:<br><br></font><font size="14" color="#ff0000ff"><b><u>Total Ballots Cast:            20<br><br></font><font size="14" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1375//380606673">Sidi'Novis Tallon</a></b></font><font size="14" color="#ff00ff00">          12</u><br></font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1383//90003608">Varos Kang</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">               6<br></font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1376//1328149095">Tandail</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">                   1<br></font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1376//1075598849">Pflepsen</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">                  1<br><br>Please joing me in shooting...er... congratulating </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1375//380606673">Sidi'Novis Tallon</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> as the new CEO of Conquering Darkness, having won a simple majority of votes.  Congrats to the others who were nominated, and a big thanks to  </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1383//90003608">Varos Kang</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> for his tenure as CEO.<br><br>Once I am duly tasked by the new leadership to send out the mail, the next round of these elections will commence with the nominations for the various director positions.  Please start thinking about the indivduals you want to help Sidi run the business and organization of this corporation.  In addition, please give some thought as to the role that you plan on playing in the corp over the near term so that we can continue to grow in size, ISK, and reputation.  Were doing great, lets keep learning, climbing, nd reaching.<br><br>In the meantime....<br><br></font><font size="14" color="#ff0000ff"><b><i>Fly it like you want it.</b></i><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Kai/Jade<br><br></font><font size="12" color="#ffff0000">--------------------------------<br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">ROCK THE VOTE !!!!   FW: Election#2: Voting for a New CEO Round 1<br>From: </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1377//92202062">Kai-Lo Darklighter</a><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Sent: 2013.09.14 04:30<br>To: Conquering Darkness, <br><br></font><font size="14" color="#ff00ff00">VOTING ENDS IN 19HRS 30 MINUTES !!! IF YO UHAVE NOT YET VOTED, PLEASE VOTE  !!! EXERCISE YOUR RIGHTS, OR LACK THEREOF !!!<br><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">--------------------------------<br>Election#2: Voting for a New CEO Round 1<br>From: </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1377//92202062">Kai-Lo Darklighter</a><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Sent: 2013.09.05 03:49<br>To: Conquering Darkness, <br><br>Greetings Corpies,<br><br>Nominations for the new CEO are now closed.   The first round of voting will begin.  Your choices for the next CEO are as follows:<br><br></font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><loc><a href="showinfo:1376//1328149095">Tandail</a><br><a href="showinfo:1375//380606673">Sidi'Novis Tallon</a><a href="showinfo:1376//1328149095"> </a><br><a href="showinfo:1383//90003608">Varos Kang</a><br><a href="showinfo:1376//1075598849">Pflepsen</a></loc><br><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">If I have missed anyone please notify me immediately and I will correct this email.<br><br>The </font><font size="12" color="#ffff0000"><b>polls are open following the receipt of this email, and will remain open for 9 Days, until 00:00 Eve Time on 15 June 2013.</b>  </font><font size="12" color="#ffffffff">Based on the turnout and pace of viting last time, this is an appropriate amount of thime.<br><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Procedures are simple, like last time...<br><br></font><font size="12" color="#ffff0000"><b>Every real person gets one vote,</b></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> that can be cast with whatever toon he or she chooses.  If I have a question as to whether a real person has been represented twice, I will raise it with the candidates.<br><br>Voting is by secret ballot (known only to me) and is simple.<br><br>Please send me an EVE Mail with</font><font size="12" color="#ff00ff00"> "OFFICIAL BALLOT for (</font><font size="12" color="#ffff00ff">insert candidate's name</font><font size="12" color="#ff00ff00">)"</font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> </font><font size="12" color="#ffffff00"><b>in the subject line.<br><br>example:  "SUBJECT: OFFICIAL BALLOT for Bob The WH GOD"<br><br></font><font size="12" color="#ff007f00">That is correct there need not be any text in the EVE Mail.</b><br><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">At the closing of the polls I will tally the number of votes.  Winner will be determined by simple plurality (greatest number) of votes cast unless all candidates or the majority corp consensus are that we should choose the winner by simple majority, that is 50% + 1,  Please let me know.<br> <br>In case of a tie..., well shit, we'll deal with that if it happens.  I do not foresee a reason to go to round two short of a tie, unless we want the next CEO to be elected with a majority of votes.  If that is the case, then we will have a run-off election with the top two vote-getters from round one.<br><br>After the CEO Election is complete, we will move to nominations for the two director positions, one of which will represent North America membership, and the other, EU/AUS/NZ, etc.  ....os so I understand.... more on that later.<br><br></font><font size="14" color="#ffff00ff"><i>Ain't democracy grand...</i><br><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Good luck to all those that have been nominated.<br><br></font><font size="14" color="#ff0000ff"><b><i>Fly like you want it....</b></i><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Kai-Lo/Jade</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="330972274"><![CDATA[Napalm Sticks to Kids <br><br>We shoot the sick, the young, the lame, <br>We do our best to maim, <br>Because the kills all count the same, <br>Napalm sticks to kids. <br><br>Chorus: Napalm sticks to kids, <br>Napalm sticks to kids. <br><br>Flying low across the trees, <br>Pilots doing what they please, <br>Dropping frags on refugees, <br>Napalm sticks to kids. <br><br>Gooks in the open, making hay, <br>But I can hear the gunships say, <br>"There'll be no Chieu Hoi today," <br>Napalm sticks to kids. <br><br>See those farmers over there, <br>Watch me get them with a pair, <br>Blood and guts just everywhere, <br>Napalm sticks to kids. <br><br>I've only seen it happen twice, <br>But both times it was mighty nice, <br>Shooting peasants planting rice, <br>Napalm sticks to kids. <br><br>Napalm, son, is lots of fun, <br>Dropped in a bomb or shot from a gun, <br>It gets the gooks when on the run, <br>Napalm sticks to kids. <br><br>Drop some napalm on a farm, <br>It won't do them any harm, <br>Just burn off their legs and arms, <br>Napalm sticks to kids. <br><br>CIA with guns for hire, <br>Montagnards around a fire, <br>Napalm makes the fire go higher, <br>Napalm sticks to kids. <br><br>I've been told it's not so neat, <br>To catch gooks burning in the street, <br>But burning flesh, it smells to sweet, <br>Napalm sticks to kids. <br><br>Children sucking on a mother's tit, <br>Wounded gooks down in a pit, <br>Dow Chemical doesn't give a shit, <br>Napalm sticks to kids. <br><br>Bombadiers don't care a bit, <br>Just as long as the pieces fit, <br>When you stuff the bodies in a pit, <br>Napalm sticks to kids. <br><br>Eighteen kids in a No Fire Zone, <br>Rooks under arms and going home, <br>Last in line goes home alone, <br>Napalm sticks to kids. <br><br>Chuck in a sampan, sitting in the stern, <br>They don't think their boats will burn, <br>Those damn gooks will never learn, <br>Napalm sticks to kids. <br><br>Cobras flying in the sun, <br>Killing gooks is lots of fun, <br>Get one pregnant and it's two for one, <br>Napalm sticks to kids. <br><br>Shoot civilians where they sit, <br>Take some pictures as you split, <br>All your life you'll remember it, <br>Napalm sticks to kids. <br><br>NVA are all hard core, <br>Flechettes never are a bore, <br>Throw those PSYOPS out the door, <br>Napalm sticks to kids. <br><br>Gather kids as you fly over town, <br>By throwing candy on the ground, <br>Then grease 'em when they gather 'round, <br>Napalm sticks to kids. ]]></row>
      <row messageID="330625383"><![CDATA[There is a new password for all towers, so don't log your alts in until you know it. I will not put the password in an email as evemail can be compromised by EveSkunk<br><br>Varos]]></row>
      <row messageID="330546489"><![CDATA[Well,  I have decided I want to go and try something else.<br><br>It has been nothing but fun, with the occaisional bumps in the road.<br><br>I have nothing but the utmost respect and admiration for all of you, and you had better keep doing what you are doing, and doing it well.<br><br>Remember, if we see each other again, you should probably shoot first :P<br><br>With much love,<br><br>Andy<br><br>P.S. Goodbye and thanks for all the fish!]]></row>
      <row messageID="330958224"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Heya Peoples,<br><br>While you might all be incredibly rich, successful, handsome, sexy and thus want to bring your T3s, I'd just like to offer a bit of perspective on why JPG III scrubs like me wouldnt mind if you brought shield recons / bombers instead.<br><br>As you all know the amount of fuel burned for bridging you is calculated mainly based on your mass. The reason this matters is because the logistics of getting fuel to where we will be staging is a huge pain.<br>For every standard </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:29988">Proteus</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> I bridge, I could bridge around about 10 bombers. Every 1600mm Armor plate you add is another 2 bombers worth of mass, and, as is needless to say I hope, your proteus won't outtank 10 bombers, nor will it outdamage even 1 bomber, nor will it be cost efficient in any relevant way shape or form. <br>For Reference: <br>10 Bombers equal about 4000DPS, 10 points, 10 potential bits of ewar, 20000EHP (coupled with locking times) and cost about 450 Mill<br>1 Proteus equals about 500DPS, 3 Points, no ewar, 100000EHP and costs about 500Mill<br>It is for this reason that I personally would prefer people bring bombers or shield fit T3's/recons (Preferably Falcons and Rapiers or Shield ECM-Gu's if you cant fly any of the others).<br><br>TLDR: Fly Bombers instead of T3's because fuel-logistics are a huge pain<br><br>Cheerio</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="330555554"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff"></font><font size="14" color="#ff00ff00">VOTING ENDS IN 19HRS 30 MINUTES !!! IF YO UHAVE NOT YET VOTED, PLEASE VOTE  !!! EXERCISE YOUR RIGHTS, OR LACK THEREOF !!!<br><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">--------------------------------<br>Election#2: Voting for a New CEO Round 1<br>From: </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1377//92202062">Kai-Lo Darklighter</a><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Sent: 2013.09.05 03:49<br>To: Conquering Darkness, <br><br>Greetings Corpies,<br><br>Nominations for the new CEO are now closed.   The first round of voting will begin.  Your choices for the next CEO are as follows:<br><br></font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><loc><a href="showinfo:1376//1328149095">Tandail</a><br><a href="showinfo:1375//380606673">Sidi'Novis Tallon</a><a href="showinfo:1376//1328149095"> </a><br><a href="showinfo:1383//90003608">Varos Kang</a></loc><br>Pflepsen<br><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">If I have missed anyone please notify me immediately and I will correct this email.<br><br>The </font><font size="12" color="#ffff0000"><b>polls are open following the receipt of this email, and will remain open for 9 Days, until 00:00 Eve Time on 15 June 2013.</b>  </font><font size="12" color="#ffffffff">Based on the turnout and pace of viting last time, this is an appropriate amount of thime.<br><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Procedures are simple, like last time...<br><br></font><font size="12" color="#ffff0000"><b>Every real person gets one vote,</b></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> that can be cast with whatever toon he or she chooses.  If I have a question as to whether a real person has been represented twice, I will raise it with the candidates.<br><br>Voting is by secret ballot (known only to me) and is simple.<br><br>Please send me an EVE Mail with</font><font size="12" color="#ff00ff00"> "OFFICIAL BALLOT for (</font><font size="12" color="#ffff00ff">insert candidate's name</font><font size="12" color="#ff00ff00">)"</font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> </font><font size="12" color="#ffffff00"><b>in the subject line.<br><br>example:  "SUBJECT: OFFICIAL BALLOT for Bob The WH GOD"<br><br></font><font size="12" color="#ff007f00">That is correct there need not be any text in the EVE Mail.</b><br><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">At the closing of the polls I will tally the number of votes.  Winner will be determined by simple plurality (greatest number) of votes cast unless all candidates or the majority corp consensus are that we should choose the winner by simple majority, that is 50% + 1,  Please let me know.<br> <br>In case of a tie..., well shit, we'll deal with that if it happens.  I do not foresee a reason to go to round two short of a tie, unless we want the next CEO to be elected with a majority of votes.  If that is the case, then we will have a run-off election with the top two vote-getters from round one.<br><br>After the CEO Election is complete, we will move to nominations for the two director positions, one of which will represent North America membership, and the other, EU/AUS/NZ, etc.  ....os so I understand.... more on that later.<br><br></font><font size="14" color="#ffff00ff"><i>Ain't democracy grand...</i><br><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Good luck to all those that have been nominated.<br><br></font><font size="14" color="#ff0000ff"><b><i>Fly like you want it....</b></i><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Kai-Lo/Jade</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="330536923"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff"></font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1373//90115305">Coriolani</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> contacted me today.<br><br>[18:59:31] Coriolani &gt; if many of your guys are near jita and on later, we could have some impromptu pew pew going on</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="330941165"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff"><br><br>--------------------------------<br>I found some things<br>From: </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1377//92638609">Lumierre Carmody</a><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Sent: 2013.09.24 04:16<br>To: </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1377//1011999887">blue coeur</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">,  <br><br>Hi there,<br><br>So I found a wreck in a wormhole. Inside the wreck there was quite a bit of loot. As the good samaritan I am, I info'd the wreck and found you to be the original owner. So, I have prepared a contract for you, with what I believe to be a fair finders fee.<br><br>Cheers,<br></font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1375//92638609">Lumierre Carmody</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> </font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="330507087"><![CDATA[Hey all,<br><br>I have successfully bullied LC into organising a Black Op on Sunday since the last time was a load of fun and I missed it and am bitter.<br><br>The idea is we get things going around 1900 Evetime so that we catch both EUTZ and USTZ, and have a bunch of people in bombers, recons and whatnot, and we kill some poor unsuspecting fools.<br><br>We will need a second covert cyno pilot though, and ideally a second Black Ops ship, so let me know if you are interested in filling any of these roles.<br><br>I do not think we need a huge number of pilots, but the more we get, the bigger the ships we get to kill.]]></row>
      <row messageID="330322745"><![CDATA[Hey guys,<br><br>As of right now the operation to bash the POCO's of LDB is off.<br><br>The french have called in serious reinforcments and we were forced out. So do not worry about alarm clocking it or prepping.<br><br>This in no way means we are done with LDB.<br><br>This is only the beginning guys, as the saying goes "They may ahve won the battle, but they have not won the war."<br><br>I will be getting in touch with allies and planning a much more agressive op for next time.<br><br>Updates will follow.<br><br>-Sidi-]]></row>
      <row messageID="330938696"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff">ALL TIMES ARE EVE TIME.<br><br>Alright guys, so here's the plan, we'll be messing around with in <loc>Geminate</loc> this weekend. Looks like there is plenty of ratting and not honestly that much pvp. Our null sec staging will be </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><loc><a href="showinfo:5//30002423">FDZ4-A</a></loc></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">. We can either bridge out of the undock or at a safe spot at the discretion of our black ops pilot and environmental conditions.<br><br>So what does this mean for you? Get your covert ops ready, bombers preferred, recons very welcome, T3's if you're a rich bastard. Try to keep it light on the T3's though, we may run into fuel issues. Also be aware that there is a chance that we all die in a fire, so keep it to what you are willing to lose (keep the +5's at home kids). The high sec bridge out will be </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><loc><a href="showinfo:5//30000156">Josameto</a></loc></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> (3 from </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><loc><a href="showinfo:5//30000142">Jita</a></loc></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">). At 1630 we will start bridging supplies to our null system. If you're in the neighborhood feel free to take the ride to the regions of danger. The last bridge out should be a 1845, so make it to high sec staging before then.<br><br>Importante:<br>If you are able and willing to fly fuel truck or light a cyno a covert cyno, please evemail me before the op. We REALLY would like another covert cyno to help out with the supplying.<br><br>Summary:<br>Hisec Bridge - </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><loc><a href="showinfo:5//30000156">Josameto</a></loc><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">NPC Null - </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><loc><a href="showinfo:5//30002423">FDZ4-A</a></loc><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Bomb Type - </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:27912">Concussion</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> (Don't expect to use these)<br><br>29 September<br>1600 - LC and Aiko Get out of Caprica<br>1630 - Supply Train Starts (Need 1 more cyno!)<br>1730 - Ensure Exit out of Caprica<br>1800 - Pflepsen Leaves to High Sec to Grab his Widow<br>1845 - Last Train Out of High Sec<br>1900 - OP Start<br><br></font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><loc><a href="showinfo:1375//92638609">Lumierre Carmody</a></loc><br><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Sidi: Feel free to forward to any allies</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="330340031"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Attached is my POV of the second fight when the frenchies had reinforcements.<br><br></font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><loc><a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S7oQ2YXP4Fg&feature=youtu.be">http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S7oQ2YXP4Fg&amp;feature=youtu.be</a></loc><br><br><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">--------------------------------<br>The French Connection<br>From: </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1377//91560447">Aiko Kurushio</a><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Sent: 2013.09.08 01:37<br>To: Conquering Darkness, <br><br>Hey Dudes and Dudettes,<br><br>As a follow up to the awesome scrap we had (the first one at least) on the French Hole, here the unedited and camera-shaky version, frapsed by yours truly (at least it's 1080p, sort of). Even though we didn't kill lots of stuff, it's still a nice watch.<br><br>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HWDKPBmnUh8<br><br>Enjoy,<br>Cheers<br><br>Aiko</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="330881817"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Our allies in LBF have found yet another carrier that needs to explode. They need a scan alt in the hole, as the one that's in there now is needed elsewhere. Anyone with a free scan alt please contact  </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1384//90115305">Coriolani</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> or  </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1377//1792168730">Smokey McWeedy</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> for details.<br><br>Varos</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="330303281"><![CDATA[Since the TS3 server kept experiencing issues in Chicago, I moved it to another state (Washington DC/Virginia).<br><br>ts22.gameservers.com:9238<br><br>or<br><br>voice.y790.info:9238  <br><br><br>password: anewday<br><br>permissions might be a bit wonky.]]></row>
      <row messageID="330800387"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Hi all,<br><br>Seeing the success and interest in black ops, I suppose we should do another. This time though I plan for us to bridge out of a npc nullsec station, so the risks run high. Bring only what you are willing to lose.<br><br>Form Up: TBD<br>Time: 1900 EVE 29 September<br><br>If you have an alliance that you would like to pick on, please eve mail me your suggestions over the next couple days. Look out for a detailed itinerary coming out this weekend.<br><br></font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1375//92638609">Lumierre Carmody</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> <br><br>PS: Sidi, feel free to forward this and the follow up itinerary to any allies that would like to join us.</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="330748839"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Greetings,<br><br>Now that we have elected a new CEO, it is time to open up the nominations for our (2) Director positions.  1 Position is for Director of the North American Time Zones, and 1 Position is for Director of the EU/AUS/NZ/South Africa Time Zones,<br><br>Anyone in the corporation may be nominated to run for one of the Director positions.  Please note however, that you must be active in that time zone otherwise, what good are ya. <br><br>To be clear we are nominating for 2 positions, so</font><font size="12" color="#ff00ff00"> everyone is free to nominate 1 candate for each position.  Each nominee will only be allowed to run for 1 of the 2 slots, so i.e. Bob cannot run for both positions.....he must pick 1 or the other 1.<br><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Starting on this </font><font size="12" color="#ffff0000">Thursday at 0000 Eve Time 19 September</font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">, and going</font><font size="12" color="#ffff0000"> until 0000 Eve Time Monday 23 September 2013, </font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">I will be accepting the nominations for candidates for these (2) Director positions for Conquering Darkness. <br><br></font><font size="12" color="#ff0000ff">To nominate someone, please simply respond to this or send me another email, and please put in the Subject Line</font><font size="12" color="#ff7f007f">,</font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> </font><font size="12" color="#ffffff00">"I nominate Bob the WH God to run for North America Director, and I nominate Bobby for EU Director."</font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">  <br><br>Yes!  That is correct... no text in the email is necessary.<br><br>After the process closes, I will issue an email with the nominees and the election procedures.  The election for the Directors will then begin on Wednesday  25 September, and run 9 days, and will end on Saturday 5 October 2013.  The process will be similar to last time.  <br><br>So to reapeat, each real person can </font><font size="12" color="#ff00ff00">nominate 1 candidate for each Director position for a total of (2) nominations, </font><font size="12" color="#ffffffff">and only I will see the nomination ballot so its quasi-secret.<br><br></font><font size="12" color="#ffff00ff">As always, anyone caught cheating will join ZePenguin in Tandail's basement.<br><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">So.... let the games begin!!!<br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br><br></font><font size="14" color="#ff0000ff"><b><i>Fly it like you want it...<br></font><font size="14" color="#ff00ff00">Kai-Lo</b></i></font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="330710193"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Dear Dudettes and Dudes,<br><br>As some of you may have noticed, the jabber signup is currently not working due to a slight snafu on somebodies end (propably mine but somebody sounds better for the moment). While I work on procrastinating/getting it fixed I'll offer my humble services as admin to manually create accounts for the moment. If you'd like to use this service, please send an email to me (or any of the following alts: </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><loc><a href="showinfo:1378//92440749">Lia Sanuki</a></loc></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">, </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><loc><a href="showinfo:1373//93080349">Martin Sonderberg</a></loc></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">, </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><loc><a href="showinfo:1385//92140930">Akane Kurushio</a></loc></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">, </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1378//92597315">Heinrich Van Schnitzel</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> or </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1378//93521700">Italian Chandelier</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">) Containing your desired username and a password you'll never ever use ever again anywhere else. In case you don't want to do that, you'll have to wait until I can be asked to fix it. <br><br>Until then, Cheerio</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="330681999"><![CDATA[WTM in it's desire to provide a better incursion community as a whole has created a new channel. "WarpTo Jita"<br><br>This trade channel has been created with the nomad incursioner in mind. The MOTD has links to the 4 major trade hubs. Got an incursion fit ship to sell? Link your contract here and hit your target market. Running ammo to make some extra iskies on the side? Offer your services up here. Looking to find Jita price on an item when you're stuck 97,282 jumps from Jita? Ask away!<br><br>Feel free to invite to this channel. While it is owned and managed by WTM, it can be of use to any incursion runner. Please be respectful in this channel. It will be governed by the same rules as WTM chat and Fleet. So have fun and don't be a dick!<br><br>Fly Safe, Fly Often,<br>Gantrithor105. ]]></row>
      <row messageID="330471329"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Thanks to the excellent work of LC, we now have a handy web app for handling the quotes of your purchase order.<br><br>Rather than send me an evemail, go to the site<br><br></font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><loc><a href="http://www.y790.org/pi/gynax.php">http://www.y790.org/pi/gynax.ph</loc>p</a><br><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">fill in the amounts etc, and you will get your quote instantly based on the prices I have loaded up (I updated them on Mondays usually). This method will also show the breakdown of the prices, so you can see exactly how the quote is calculated.<br><br>Ideally, if more people want to get in on this gig, we (and by that I mean LC) will allow multiple buyers.<br><br>Anyway, give it a go, let me know if you have any questions or issues, and most importantly of all, give me a couple of days to get the ISK together...</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="330321734"><![CDATA[Hey Dudes and Dudettes,<br><br>As a follow up to the awesome scrap we had (the first one at least) on the French Hole, here the unedited and camera-shaky version, frapsed by yours truly (at least it's 1080p, sort of). Even though we didn't kill lots of stuff, it's still a nice watch.<br><br>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HWDKPBmnUh8<br><br>Enjoy,<br>Cheers<br><br>Aiko]]></row>
    </rowset>
  </result>
  <cachedUntil>2023-09-30 11:05:28</cachedUntil>
</eveapi>