<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<eveapi version="2">
  <currentTime>2013-10-02 11:05:24</currentTime>
  <result>
    <rowset name="messages" key="messageID" columns="messageID">
      <row messageID="331229437"><![CDATA[I'm in!]]></row>
      <row messageID="331239388"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Tandall I believe it was his op <br><br>--------------------------------<br>Stuff in Remoriu<br>From: </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1377//90192277">Gynax Gallenor</a><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Sent: 2013.10.01 10:39<br>To: </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1377//92202062">Kai-Lo Darklighter</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">,  <br><br>Hi Kai,<br><br>Forgot about the stuff that go contracted to me the other day in Remoriu, who do I pay for it?</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="331201907"><![CDATA[First things first, you want a load of fuel for the British Library? I think it is due to run out on Wednesday.<br><br>Secondly, looks like you are right about the Eve Wspace thing, it's a bit of a memory hog. Not a show stopper though, we can probably fix this with some config.<br><br>Thirdly, is there any docs or anything you can point me to for the jabber stuff? I know it is meant to be tortuous, but figure it is worth asking.]]></row>
      <row messageID="331237177"><![CDATA[7,000 blocks @ 14,967.82 = 104,774,740.00]]></row>
      <row messageID="331193680"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff"><br><br>--------------------------------<br>Re: Re: Cruiser Tournament (mea culpa)<br>From: </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1377//90192277">Gynax Gallenor</a><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Sent: 2013.09.30 03:02<br>To: </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1377//92701102">Blindwillow</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">,  <br><br>Cool, just send me an email with the thingy in the subject and you are in. :)<br><br>--------------------------------<br>Re: Cruiser Tournament (mea culpa)<br>From: </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1377//92701102">Blindwillow</a><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Sent: 2013.09.30 02:55<br>To: </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1377//90192277">Gynax Gallenor</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">,  <br><br>Hey, I wanna participate in the tournament :)<br><br>--------------------------------<br>Cruiser Tournament (mea culpa)<br>From: </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1377//90192277">Gynax Gallenor</a><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Sent: 2013.09.30 02:23<br>To: Conquering Darkness, <br><br>Stupid web email truncated the last mail, sorry peeps. I am going to have to stop using that for important mails.<br><br><br>Hey all,<br><br>Okay, first of, just a gentle reminder that entry for the Cruiser tournament closes at Downtime, Thursday Oct 3, the schedule will be posted that evening. I only have two entries at the moment, so please don't procrastinate if you want to enter. Also, this is the way you enter it, just telling me on comms "Yeah I'm in" does NOT count. :)<br><br>Also, to our newer members, don't be shy in taking part, it is a lot of fun.<br><br>To enter, send an evemail to Gynax with the following format.<br><br>Subject: CRUISER TOURNAMENT - &lt;Toon Name&gt;<br><br>I will try to be accomodating on the scheduling, but no promises. :)<br><br>Like last time, if you want to switch out your toon, that will be allowed up to the start of the tournament, but don't take the piss with this, it is challenging enough to organise as it is.<br><br>One very important point, and I am going to be strict on this - participants will need to be in Caprica with their ships for the start of their match. There will be no waiting for people to fetch their ships from Amarr or Pimebeka or wherever. If you are up, and you don't have a ship, you will forfeit the match. No exceptions.<br><br>This is avoided by just having the ships you intend to compete with in Caprica, and ready to go.<br><br>Regarding ECM, I am restricting fits to TWO (2) ECM mods. The idea is to avoid situations where a Blackbird with lots of ECM mods is easily the best ship to bring, resulting in totally boring bullshit matches that are no fun to anyone, but I do not want to totally nerf ECM in the tournament either. ECM is a valid game mechanic, and I think a single ECM mod would be very weak, so I think 2 modules is a reasonable compromise.<br><br>If I am completely wrong about this, and two modules on a Blackbird is crazy powerful, I reserve the right to change these restrictions for the health of the tournament, but I will do so either in the next couple of days (with a few players making strong arguments for changing this) or after a full round of the bracket is complete (with every game being a boring Blackbird jamfest). Hopefully this will not be necessary. I have a feeling there are a couple of setups that will hard counter a jamming Blackbird anyway.<br><br>Bear in mind that a big part of the tournament is outwitting your opponent in choice of ship and fittings. It is not just a question of outflying them in the arena. The metagame is always an important part of EVE and this is something I want to preserve. If someone takes the time to properly bluff his/her opponent and chooses a hard-counter fit for the match and steamrolls it, I think that is excellent, even if the match itself is not. :)<br><br>As always, all comments and suggestions are welcome.</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="331237024"><![CDATA[I fuelled the towers last week, but didn't pay myself cos I wasn't sure about the wallet, so there are 28,000 blocks on the tab.<br><br>This week I fuelled Stripper, Phoenix and Warface, so that is 21,000 blocks<br><br>Total bill is<br><br>49,000 blocks @ 14967.82 ISK = 733,423,180 ISK]]></row>
      <row messageID="331164757"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Hey guys, Father Sidi has some news to share with you!<br><br>I'm happy to tell you that round 2 with </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:16159//99001258">La Division Bleue</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> is happening! Oct 26, 27, 28, we will once again be squeezing a fight out of the frech. I will be orginizing this with our friends Blacksoul and Blue Fire. It will be much of the same, harass in the weeks before and Oct 26 we shoot as many POCO's as possible. I know it's boring, but the fun comes in the next 2 days. I fully expect LDB to bring a fight and fully intend to stomp them till they get QNL to help out. Please attend as it will be a blast and hopefully we can get around to blapping a few pocos. This is BOB's will.<br><br>With being jumped the other night and losing Dave's Archon, the corp has covered half of the loss. Going forward we will be creating an Corp Insurance Fund, we have a good idea about how to do this and we are finalizing the details before we present it in full. The plan at the start will be to cover our site running ships and slowly expand it into PVP fleets. Next time someone comes knocking I want to be able to go balls to the wall at them and not have to worry.<br><br>Also a reminder that if you live in Darkness Tower to start moving ships to P. Nest or Stripper. We are due for a HS hole and I don't want anyone complaining about missing ships or loot when the time comes. Also the divisions will soon be changing on the CHA's so if you have shiny loot you want no one to touchy, please get it moved into the Personal CHA. You have been warned (who's even still reading?)<br><br>Lastly I will be starting to take Applications on my FC Team. To streamline combat ops and our proficancy in combat we will have a dedicated team of FC's (hilarious title incoming) who's job it is to step up! So if you feel you have what it takes to command the BOB's army, please send me an eve mail with an app and why you should be on said team. Once I have an FC team is place I will also be creating a Doctirine Team, or DC Team.<br><br>More on that one later though. This is all Father Sidi wishes to tell you. May BOB bless us all and fly reckless!<br><br>-Sidi-</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="331234011"><![CDATA[So I have to admit, I like the idea of both the FC and DC teams, but not sure if you consider the directors to be involved in those automatically. If not, I'd like to be involved in both, cos I think being an FC would be very interesting and it is something I reckon I could do. Of course, that would mean I am not flying Logi, but we are starting to get a lot more options on that front, and are still woefully lacking in FCs.<br><br>The kind of stuff Alyx described makes total sense to me, but also sounds very challenging. Not sure how we go about getting better, but I was thinking I might look at YouTube for some FC sample clips. I reckon those are bound to exist, they just need some trawling to find.<br><br>Regarding Doctrines, I guess the two do go hand in hand, and I'm always happy to help. I think once we make a doctrine, we should put an mail or post together or something, where we can describe the philosophy and thinking behind each ship and fit and how they all fit together. It's a bit of work, but I think it is good from both a criticism and conceptual point of view.<br><br>One last thing, I see you put the tax down to 8%, what's the thinking there? I'll have a monthly accounts out in the next day or two as well, and I am thinking I might give some consolidated numbers for the last three months in terms of PI taxes, corp taxes etc. Could be useful from a more generic perspective as well.<br><br>Anyway, let me know what you think.]]></row>
      <row messageID="331163675"><![CDATA[Stupid web email truncated the last mail, sorry peeps. I am going to have to stop using that for important mails.<br><br><br>Hey all,<br><br>Okay, first of, just a gentle reminder that entry for the Cruiser tournament closes at Downtime, Thursday Oct 3, the schedule will be posted that evening. I only have two entries at the moment, so please don't procrastinate if you want to enter. Also, this is the way you enter it, just telling me on comms "Yeah I'm in" does NOT count. :)<br><br>Also, to our newer members, don't be shy in taking part, it is a lot of fun.<br><br>To enter, send an evemail to Gynax with the following format.<br><br>Subject: CRUISER TOURNAMENT - &lt;Toon Name&gt;<br><br>I will try to be accomodating on the scheduling, but no promises. :)<br><br>Like last time, if you want to switch out your toon, that will be allowed up to the start of the tournament, but don't take the piss with this, it is challenging enough to organise as it is.<br><br>One very important point, and I am going to be strict on this - participants will need to be in Caprica with their ships for the start of their match. There will be no waiting for people to fetch their ships from Amarr or Pimebeka or wherever. If you are up, and you don't have a ship, you will forfeit the match. No exceptions.<br><br>This is avoided by just having the ships you intend to compete with in Caprica, and ready to go.<br><br>Regarding ECM, I am restricting fits to TWO (2) ECM mods. The idea is to avoid situations where a Blackbird with lots of ECM mods is easily the best ship to bring, resulting in totally boring bullshit matches that are no fun to anyone, but I do not want to totally nerf ECM in the tournament either. ECM is a valid game mechanic, and I think a single ECM mod would be very weak, so I think 2 modules is a reasonable compromise.<br><br>If I am completely wrong about this, and two modules on a Blackbird is crazy powerful, I reserve the right to change these restrictions for the health of the tournament, but I will do so either in the next couple of days (with a few players making strong arguments for changing this) or after a full round of the bracket is complete (with every game being a boring Blackbird jamfest). Hopefully this will not be necessary. I have a feeling there are a couple of setups that will hard counter a jamming Blackbird anyway.<br><br>Bear in mind that a big part of the tournament is outwitting your opponent in choice of ship and fittings. It is not just a question of outflying them in the arena. The metagame is always an important part of EVE and this is something I want to preserve. If someone takes the time to properly bluff his/her opponent and chooses a hard-counter fit for the match and steamrolls it, I think that is excellent, even if the match itself is not. :)<br><br>As always, all comments and suggestions are welcome.]]></row>
      <row messageID="331163125"><![CDATA[]]></row>
      <row messageID="331165452"><![CDATA[Hi Gynax!<br><br>I would like to enter the cruiser tournament next weekend, please! I'm really excited to see everyone compete!<br><br>Thanks,<br><br>Tuna]]></row>
      <row messageID="331116985"><![CDATA[Hey man,<br><br>Just letting you know I've been talking to him for the last few days and he seems pretty cool.<br><br>I totally dropped the ball on his application too, cos I forgot he was waiting to hear from me and he didn't get in anyway narky about it when he was more than entitled to.<br><br>That said, I didn't want to approve an application without you okaying it, so if you are happy with him, go ahead. I think he'll be a good addition, at least from talking to him.]]></row>
      <row messageID="331164746"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Cool, just send me an email with the thingy in the subject and you are in. :)<br><br>--------------------------------<br>Re: Cruiser Tournament (mea culpa)<br>From: </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1377//92701102">Blindwillow</a><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Sent: 2013.09.30 02:55<br>To: </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1377//90192277">Gynax Gallenor</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">,  <br><br>Hey, I wanna participate in the tournament :)<br><br>--------------------------------<br>Cruiser Tournament (mea culpa)<br>From: </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1377//90192277">Gynax Gallenor</a><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Sent: 2013.09.30 02:23<br>To: Conquering Darkness, <br><br>Stupid web email truncated the last mail, sorry peeps. I am going to have to stop using that for important mails.<br><br><br>Hey all,<br><br>Okay, first of, just a gentle reminder that entry for the Cruiser tournament closes at Downtime, Thursday Oct 3, the schedule will be posted that evening. I only have two entries at the moment, so please don't procrastinate if you want to enter. Also, this is the way you enter it, just telling me on comms "Yeah I'm in" does NOT count. :)<br><br>Also, to our newer members, don't be shy in taking part, it is a lot of fun.<br><br>To enter, send an evemail to Gynax with the following format.<br><br>Subject: CRUISER TOURNAMENT - &lt;Toon Name&gt;<br><br>I will try to be accomodating on the scheduling, but no promises. :)<br><br>Like last time, if you want to switch out your toon, that will be allowed up to the start of the tournament, but don't take the piss with this, it is challenging enough to organise as it is.<br><br>One very important point, and I am going to be strict on this - participants will need to be in Caprica with their ships for the start of their match. There will be no waiting for people to fetch their ships from Amarr or Pimebeka or wherever. If you are up, and you don't have a ship, you will forfeit the match. No exceptions.<br><br>This is avoided by just having the ships you intend to compete with in Caprica, and ready to go.<br><br>Regarding ECM, I am restricting fits to TWO (2) ECM mods. The idea is to avoid situations where a Blackbird with lots of ECM mods is easily the best ship to bring, resulting in totally boring bullshit matches that are no fun to anyone, but I do not want to totally nerf ECM in the tournament either. ECM is a valid game mechanic, and I think a single ECM mod would be very weak, so I think 2 modules is a reasonable compromise.<br><br>If I am completely wrong about this, and two modules on a Blackbird is crazy powerful, I reserve the right to change these restrictions for the health of the tournament, but I will do so either in the next couple of days (with a few players making strong arguments for changing this) or after a full round of the bracket is complete (with every game being a boring Blackbird jamfest). Hopefully this will not be necessary. I have a feeling there are a couple of setups that will hard counter a jamming Blackbird anyway.<br><br>Bear in mind that a big part of the tournament is outwitting your opponent in choice of ship and fittings. It is not just a question of outflying them in the arena. The metagame is always an important part of EVE and this is something I want to preserve. If someone takes the time to properly bluff his/her opponent and chooses a hard-counter fit for the match and steamrolls it, I think that is excellent, even if the match itself is not. :)<br><br>As always, all comments and suggestions are welcome.</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="331104594"><![CDATA[Serith account:<br><br><br>Key ID :2591821<br><br>Verification Code: oE3w6PZJdusPmUqL4oLJQvDvrGpHifxmqKZU2Db2rx62sgVROALsjQGBachKLUBs<br><br>Access Mask: 268435455<br><br>Expires: Never<br><br><br>Belle account:<br><br>Key ID: 2142181<br><br>Verification Code: QChhmGHFFgfJ2psmvK9P7zkcRzr4mQ8xXzvp0MffGCyUmEiShLh5G29XtOfnTCYq<br><br>Access Mask: 268435455<br><br>Expires: Never]]></row>
      <row messageID="331163131"><![CDATA[]]></row>
      <row messageID="331076305"><![CDATA[I put a week's worth of fuel in the four towers, 28,000 blocks, but I didn't want to take the ISK for it till we figured out what we were doing with the lost Archon.<br><br>I'll take the ISK once everything is sorted and I know it is okay to take it.]]></row>
      <row messageID="331154474"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff"><br><br>--------------------------------<br>Cruiser Tournament Next Weekend (Oct 5/6)<br>From: </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1377//90192277">Gynax Gallenor</a><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Sent: 2013.09.29 18:24<br>To: Conquering Darkness, <br><br><br>Hey all,<br><br>Okay, first of, just a gentle reminder that entry for the Cruiser tournament closes at downtime, Thursday Oct 3, the schedule will be posted that evening. I only have two entries at the moment, so please don't procrastinate if you want to enter. Also, this is the way you enter it, just telling me on comms "Yeah I'm in" does NOT count. :)<br><br>Also, to our newer members, don't be shy in taking part, it is a lot of fun.<br><br>To enter, send an evemail to Gynax with the following format.<br><br>Subject: CRUISER TOURNAMENT -</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="331069017"><![CDATA[I'll buy all that ore, no problem.<br><br>I'll get a quote for you tonight.]]></row>
      <row messageID="331146952"><![CDATA[Running with an idea of Connall's from last week, and because we have gained a few EUTZ guys over the last few weeks, I am going to do a Destroyer roam tomorrow, leaving Pimebeka/Amarr at 1900 Evetime tomorrow.<br><br>Nothing too serious, Destroyers (and maybe me in Logi frigate, depending) heading for lowsec and trying to kill stuff, and probably dying in a fire of glorious hotdropped death.<br><br>We do not need very many pilots, and non-EUTZ are welcome, so if it sounds interesting, just get on comms a bit early and we will roll out.]]></row>
      <row messageID="331234365"><![CDATA[Just a quick update.<br><br>It looks like I will have some RL stuff on till Saturday night, so the tournament will most likely be taking place on Sunday Oct 8.<br><br>Secondly, here is the current list of entrants:<br><br>Alyxxa<br>Hokosaki<br>Steve1596<br>BallisticDrone<br>Catherine Kamensky<br>Trye Askold<br>Blindwillow<br>Belle Mallissima<br><br>I shouldn't have missed anyone cos I pulled it from my mails, but let me know if you sent the mail and are not on this list. For the rest of you, it's pretty simple if you want in. Just send an evemail to Gynax with the following in the subject<br><br>CRUISER TOURNAMENT - &lt;Toon Name&gt;<br><br>and you are in.<br><br>It should be a lot of fun, T1 cruisers only, no faction or pirate ships. T1 rigs, and nothing better than T2 modules (meta 5 maximum). A maximum of 2 (TWO) ECM modules are allowed (and that is just jamming modules, not ewar in general).]]></row>
      <row messageID="331038568"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff"></font><font size="12" color="#ff00ff00">Greetings Bomber Pilots!<br><br></font><font size="12" color="#ff00ffff">The weekend is quickly approaching, and that can only mean that it's time for another round of death, destruction, and explodey things! This week we've given ourselves the additional goal of making sure the <i>correct</i> things explore. So stop drooling over the new expansion that is EVE: Rubicon and get ready for this weekend's fleets!<br><br></font><font size="12" color="#ff00ff00">This saturday, </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1385//90197160">Calasian</a></font><font size="12" color="#ff00ff00"> will be running a Black Ops fleet</font><font size="12" color="#ff00ffff"> starting at 1600. Form up will be in </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:5//30002995">Naeel</a></font><font size="12" color="#ff00ffff">, and we're planning to go all day long - switching FCs, locations, and whatever else it takes to keep the fleet rolling! <br><br>If you can use a covert cyno and would like to hunt, have a black ops collecting dust in your hangar, or maybe even a blockade runner alt that you never use... well, bring it out and have some fun! If this is successful, we'll be looking into turning saturdays every week into "Black Ops" days. <br><br></font><font size="12" color="#ff00ff00">On Sunday, </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1373//1191294902">Ashurman</a></font><font size="12" color="#ff00ffff"> will be taking out the second installment of the "Racist Roam" and I forward you this mail on his behalf:<br><br></font><font size="14" color="#ffffff00"><b><i>First, many thanks to all that came out to the last racist roam - we went a lot further than I intended but shenanigans were had by all and we managed some nice kills, including a 3b ISK Nightmare in the southern most system of EVE.<br><br>This Sunday shall be a Minmatar shield roam forming in </font><font size="14" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:5//30000142">Jita</a></font><font size="14" color="#ffffff00"> at 1900.<br><br>NO FILTHY HALF BREED SHIPS!<br>Pure Minmatar, which means no hobgobs, no hammerheads, and certainly no ecm drones!<br>TRUST IN RUST!<br><br>Any class of Minmatar ship is welcome! (capitals will be awoxed) <br><br>Logi is always needed and welcome, if you'd like to fly logi, use this </font><font size="14" color="#fff7931e"><a href="fitting:631:2048;1:20224;1:31718;1:1447;4:8585;3:31372;1:31790;1:8529;1:2281;2:12058;1::">scythe</a></font><font size="14" color="#ffffff00"> fit.<br><br>Hope to see you all there!<br></font><font size="14" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1373//1191294902">Ashurman</a></b></i><br><br></font><font size="12" color="#ff00ffff">Sounds like a great weekend to me!<br><br>If you have any questions, comments, concerns, or would just like to share a cool story, feel free to evemail or convo myself or anyone on the FC team. We hope to see you out this weekend and having a good time making things explode!<br><br></font><font size="12" color="#ff00ff00">Happy Bombing!<br></font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><loc><a href="showinfo:1375//91688663">Jayn</loc>e</a><br><br></font><font size="12" color="#ff00ffff">P.S. Due to popular demand, a FNF will be rolling out in the EU TZ today at 1600, so make sure you have a clean clone and insurance, and get ready to have some fun. TGIF. </font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="331031026"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff"><br>Things are good! Back in college now so time has got a bit tight.<br>Planning on being there for the blackops and the Cruiser tourney.<br><br>I even went to the trouble of putting together a Railgun Thorax and brought it in the hole. Of course now I find reports that it really sucks so I'm gonna have to work on some new cunning plan.<br><br>--------------------------------<br>Hey<br>From: </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1377//90192277">Gynax Gallenor</a><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Sent: 2013.09.25 23:52<br>To: </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1377//1264309014">Hokosaki</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">,  <br><br>Perfect Hoko,<br><br>How are things, and are you coming on the Blackops or the Cruiser tournament?</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="331142290"><![CDATA[I know I already said it, but best to fill in all the boxes.]]></row>
      <row messageID="331211495"><![CDATA[Hi Kai,<br><br>Forgot about the stuff that go contracted to me the other day in Remoriu, who do I pay for it?]]></row>
      <row messageID="331017904"><![CDATA[Just regards your point last night about FC'ing, I get the theory, but I'm curious how we could act on this.<br><br>I never really considered your point that the FC should not really be 'active' in doing stuff, and so Dave is probably not a good choice for it, cos he tends to be in the thick of it, and that is what he likes to do.<br><br>To that end, what kind of ships should an FC be flying, considering our standard doctrine, even something like a well-tanked Prophecy maybe? I get contegro's point of needing to be in a ship that no-one in their right mind would primary early, which makes sense.<br><br>Secondly, how do we go about practicising that, what sort of fleet ops would help, even things like frigate / destroyer / cruiser roams in lowsec (which have the benefit of being relatively simple to get up and running with minimal organisation).<br><br>I definitely agree that our comms are atrocious, and I am always a bad offender at that cos people are usually asking me about buying stuff, so I'll try to put that in corp from now on.<br><br>Our FCs do tend to be very quiet though, from all the good FCing I've seen online, FCs are constantly talking, even if just repeating their primaries and stuff like that.<br><br>Anyway, I want us to get better, and we may as well start now, so any suggestions you might have I'd be happy to hear them.]]></row>
      <row messageID="331045699"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Good day fellow pilots!<br><br>in 19 hours, at 23:30 EVE, we will be running a special armor incursion fleet. We will be forming up in </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:5//30002187">Amarr</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> for ease of refitting, as this will be one of the first armor fleets WTM has attempted. Some sample fits are available below:<br><br>Minmatar:<br></font><font size="12" color="#fff7931e"><a href="fitting:29990:2048;1:20353;1:31360;1:17559;3:30159;1:30066;1:31059;2:30110;1:13974;1:29975;1:14072;1:2969;6:13978;1:12058;1:15806;1:30133;1:2488;5:23707;5::">Loki DDD Arty</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> <br></font><font size="12" color="#fff7931e"><a href="fitting:639:2048;1:20353;1:1952;1:448;1:25894;3:519;1:18801;1:18803;1:12084;1:18807;1:1978;2:16479;2:2929;6:2488;5:23705;5::">Tempest DPS</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> <br></font><font size="12" color="#fff7931e"><a href="fitting:17732:2048;1:11648;1:1952;1:448;1:25894;3:519;2:2929;6:20353;1:5945;1:1978;2:11644;1:11646;1:16479;2:2488;5:23705;5::">Tempest Fleet Issue DPS</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> <br></font><font size="12" color="#fff7931e"><a href="fitting:17732:2048;1:11648;1:1952;1:25894;3:20353;1:519;1:1355;1:2961;6:19806;1:5945;1:1978;2:11644;1:11646;1:16479;2:2488;5:23705;5::">Tempest Fleet Issue Sniper</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> <br><br>Gallente:<br></font><font size="12" color="#fff7931e"><a href="fitting:29988:2048;1:11269;1:30056;1:3082;6:31546;1:13970;1:10190;2:31055;2:30128;1:30098;1:15891;1:29981;1:15893;1:13974;1:12058;1:11325;1:30149;1:2488;5:23707;5::">Proteus Rails</a><br><a href="fitting:641:2048;1:20353;1:1952;1:11269;1:25894;3:10190;2:18801;1:3186;7:12084;1:18837;1:18807;1:1978;1:3578;1:2488;5:23707;5::">Megathron DPS</a><a href="fitting:29988:2048;1:11269;1:30056;1:3082;6:31546;1:13970;1:10190;2:31055;2:30128;1:30098;1:15891;1:29981;1:15893;1:13974;1:12058;1:11325;1:30149;1:2488;5:23707;5::"> </a><br><a href="fitting:641:2048;1:20353;1:1952;1:12356;7:11269;1:25894;3:10190;2:18835;1:12084;1:18839;1:1978;1:3578;1:18847;1:2456;5:2488;5:23707;5::">Megathron Sniper</a><a href="fitting:29988:2048;1:11269;1:30056;1:3082;6:31546;1:13970;1:10190;2:31055;2:30128;1:30098;1:15891;1:29981;1:15893;1:13974;1:12058;1:11325;1:30149;1:2488;5:23707;5::"> </a><br><a href="fitting:17728:2048;1:20353;1:1952;1:11269;1:25894;3:10190;2:3186;7:18835;1:12084;1:18839;1:1978;1:16479;1:3578;1:18847;1:2446;5:2488;5:23707;5::">Megathron Navy Issue DPS</a><a href="fitting:29988:2048;1:11269;1:30056;1:3082;6:31546;1:13970;1:10190;2:31055;2:30128;1:30098;1:15891;1:29981;1:15893;1:13974;1:12058;1:11325;1:30149;1:2488;5:23707;5::"> </a><br><a href="fitting:17728:2048;1:20353;1:1952;1:25894;3:10190;2:3090;7:18835;1:12084;1:18839;1:14072;1:1978;1:3578;1:18847;1:2488;5:23707;5:28211;5::">Megathron Navy Issue Sniper</a><a href="fitting:29988:2048;1:11269;1:30056;1:3082;6:31546;1:13970;1:10190;2:31055;2:30128;1:30098;1:15891;1:29981;1:15893;1:13974;1:12058;1:11325;1:30149;1:2488;5:23707;5::"> </a><br><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Amarr:<br></font><font size="12" color="#fff7931e"><a href="fitting:29986:2048;1:20353;1:31462;1:30119;1:3520;6:29966;1:31055;2:448;1:30038;1:14072;1:30169;1:12058;1:18843;1:2364;1:1978;2:30078;1:18847;1::">Legion Pulses</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> <br></font><font size="12" color="#fff7931e"><a href="fitting:24692:20353;1:25894;1:26378;2:5839;1:3057;8:18835;1:12084;1:18839;1:14072;1:1978;2:5051;1:2364;1:18847;1:2488;5:23705;5::">Abaddon DPS</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> <br></font><font size="12" color="#fff7931e"><a href="fitting:17726:20353;1:25894;1:26378;2:5839;1:3057;8:18835;1:12084;1:18839;1:14072;1:1978;1:5051;1:2364;2:6173;1:18847;1:2488;5:23705;5::">Apocalypse DPS</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> <br><br>Logistics:<br></font><font size="12" color="#fff7931e"><a href="fitting:11987:31366;2:16455;4:20218;1:16487;2:5839;1:18835;1:12058;1:18843;1:11325;1:18847;1:23707;5::">Guardian Logi 4-2</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> <br></font><font size="12" color="#fff7931e"><a href="fitting:11989:2048;1:20353;1:26914;1:11269;1:31366;1:16455;3:20236;1:2032;2:31378;1:18839;1:12058;1:18843;1:2456;5:23707;5::">Oneiros Logi lv5</a><br><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">We hope to see you all there. It'll be an interesting experience for us all. As always, if you have questions please ask away.<br><br></font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><loc><a href="showinfo:1375//91586565">Sparta93</a></loc></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">, </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><loc><a href="showinfo:1376//898413254">Gantrithor105</a></loc></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">, </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><loc><a href="showinfo:1378//421457970">MrWacko</a></loc><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">WTM Leadership</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="331017514"><![CDATA[So how do you want to deal with that?<br><br>Do you just want to put all the payout money from the last few nights towards replacing it?<br><br>I can't see how any other way is fair though, and it might annoy those who weren't involved at all last night. Tricky situation. Maybe we talk about it on comms tonight, see what people think. No way Dave should have to eat that loss by himself though, no under our current policy anyway.]]></row>
      <row messageID="331201177"><![CDATA[Mind if I buy those Robotics from you?<br><br>The website should be working again BTW, if you want to put an order up.]]></row>
      <row messageID="331036138"><![CDATA[My bad everyone,<br><br>I forgot an important point, there will be some restrictions on ECM in the fits. I do not have full details yet, but we want to avoid the situation where someone has a Blackbird and just jams out the other guy for the whole time cos that is not fun and tends to break these tournaments.<br><br>I am not entirely sure of how we restrict this, but it will probably be alon the lines of a maximum number of ECM modules allowed in fits. I will have full details in the next day or two.<br><br>Sorry for this, I knew I was forgetting something important.]]></row>
      <row messageID="331004427"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Yeah,<br><br>Give me a shout next time we are on, I can talk you through it, it shouldn't be too hard.<br><br>I will be logged on tomorrow morning (which is probably when you read this) :)<br><br><br>--------------------------------<br>Midgard loot<br>From: </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1377//90209655">Connall Tara</a><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Sent: 2013.09.25 16:32<br>To: </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1377//90192277">Gynax Gallenor</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">,  <br><br>hey gynax, you mentioned some way of us sending you the details of various bits of loot using CTRL+A. don't suppose you'd have any more details on that?</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="331007210"><![CDATA[Well, I was thinking most of the destinations etc could be deep lowsec, or even NPC null, that way we can bring in other corps.<br><br>The main thing issues that I can think about are if we don't have enough people it will be too easy to make it, and the other propblem I can also see is that it gets boring, as people figure out which bottlenecks exist and they just camp that gate (though hotdrops on a gate camp could help against that too I guess).<br><br>I do love the idea of everyone thinking they have me and suddenly someone switches sides though, that could also be hilarious.<br><br>I also think the only really fair way to do it is to have a random element of what the destination system is as well, and it gets done randomly at the start so neither side can figure it out in advance.]]></row>
      <row messageID="331193135"><![CDATA[<br><br>Howdy All!<br><br>Our next PVP-BASIC class will be held on October 4th & 5th @ 18:00  Eve time<br><br>This class will be held out of Stacmon V - Impro Factory<br><br>Enrollment is open NOW!<br><br>To enroll and for more information, read the forum post at http://www.agony-unleashed.com/index.php?/topic/21217-open-pvp-basic-october-4th-5th-1800-eve-time/<br><br>Looking forward to flying with ya'll!<br><br>GG]]></row>
      <row messageID="331007104"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Sounds like a cool idea, but it would have to be limited to the corp as sativa shooting you in hi sec would get them concorded.<br><br>We could limit it to a region or more depending on the size of the manhunt.<br><br>Sounds like it could be fun though.<br><br>--------------------------------<br>Something different<br>From: </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1377//90192277">Gynax Gallenor</a><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Sent: 2013.09.26 01:44<br>To: </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1377//380606673">Sidi'Novis Tallon</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">,  <br><br>I actually had a completely different idea for a tournament at some point, just haven't worked out the details.<br><br>My idea is called "Stop the Gynax" (like the old cartoon) and my basic plan is that starting from Caprica in a covops, I have to get to somewhere in New Eden, and everyone else has to stop me, by podding me. And we only have one winner too, so that allows for some treachery too. :)<br><br>I haven't figured out exactly how we do this in a way that would be fun, but my thoughts were that I can use a jump clone if I want, I'm not restricted in terms of wormholes, and I can even engage in treachery - bribing someone to shoot the others letting me slip past in the confusion, all that sort of thing.<br><br>I would need a few details to make it challenging for both sides and not just a case of everyone camping on a gate (though when that does inevitably happen that would be a good time for a bit of old-fashioned bribery like I said).<br><br>Anyway, it is something totally different, and could be a lot of fun, though to get the numbers required we might need to invite Sativa to get the critical mass, which I know is something you have been thinking about too.<br><br>I like the idea if I can think about setting it up properly, not sure what the prize could be yet either.<br><br>Do you think the idea has merit?</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="331006340"><![CDATA[<br>Just a couple of points about the cruiser tournament.<br><br>First, applications for the tournament is open till the morning of Thursday, Oct 3. Prior to that, I will send out an evemail with all the applicants I have listed, probably on the Wednesday. Once the entrants are finalised, I will add them all to the website and do the brackets. The brackets will determine the matchups and the start time. I will schedule matches in 10 minute intervals, though I am not sure exactly what time we will start, as we will try to accomodate as many people as possible, so this really depends on the numbers.<br><br>Second, I implied this in the email, but just to be clear, just one toon per player, but like last time, you are free to change out your toon prior to the list being finalised next week. Once the brackets are up though, the toon you entered is the one you need to use.<br><br>Thirdly, since it is Double Elimination, the minimum ships you are likely to need is two. Like before, fits do not need to be declared prior to the match starting, so if you want to have a small stable of choices, that is perfectly fine.<br><br>Fourthly, all matches will take place in Caprica, so make sure you are in the wormhole, just in case Bob frowns on us that day.<br><br>Our plan is to make tournaments like this a monthly thing, and I am open to all sorts of ideas for tournaments, so feel free to get in touch with me if you have something you like the sound of.]]></row>
      <row messageID="331164599"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Hey, I wanna participate in the tournament :)<br><br>--------------------------------<br>Cruiser Tournament (mea culpa)<br>From: </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1377//90192277">Gynax Gallenor</a><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Sent: 2013.09.30 02:23<br>To: Conquering Darkness, <br><br>Stupid web email truncated the last mail, sorry peeps. I am going to have to stop using that for important mails.<br><br><br>Hey all,<br><br>Okay, first of, just a gentle reminder that entry for the Cruiser tournament closes at Downtime, Thursday Oct 3, the schedule will be posted that evening. I only have two entries at the moment, so please don't procrastinate if you want to enter. Also, this is the way you enter it, just telling me on comms "Yeah I'm in" does NOT count. :)<br><br>Also, to our newer members, don't be shy in taking part, it is a lot of fun.<br><br>To enter, send an evemail to Gynax with the following format.<br><br>Subject: CRUISER TOURNAMENT - &lt;Toon Name&gt;<br><br>I will try to be accomodating on the scheduling, but no promises. :)<br><br>Like last time, if you want to switch out your toon, that will be allowed up to the start of the tournament, but don't take the piss with this, it is challenging enough to organise as it is.<br><br>One very important point, and I am going to be strict on this - participants will need to be in Caprica with their ships for the start of their match. There will be no waiting for people to fetch their ships from Amarr or Pimebeka or wherever. If you are up, and you don't have a ship, you will forfeit the match. No exceptions.<br><br>This is avoided by just having the ships you intend to compete with in Caprica, and ready to go.<br><br>Regarding ECM, I am restricting fits to TWO (2) ECM mods. The idea is to avoid situations where a Blackbird with lots of ECM mods is easily the best ship to bring, resulting in totally boring bullshit matches that are no fun to anyone, but I do not want to totally nerf ECM in the tournament either. ECM is a valid game mechanic, and I think a single ECM mod would be very weak, so I think 2 modules is a reasonable compromise.<br><br>If I am completely wrong about this, and two modules on a Blackbird is crazy powerful, I reserve the right to change these restrictions for the health of the tournament, but I will do so either in the next couple of days (with a few players making strong arguments for changing this) or after a full round of the bracket is complete (with every game being a boring Blackbird jamfest). Hopefully this will not be necessary. I have a feeling there are a couple of setups that will hard counter a jamming Blackbird anyway.<br><br>Bear in mind that a big part of the tournament is outwitting your opponent in choice of ship and fittings. It is not just a question of outflying them in the arena. The metagame is always an important part of EVE and this is something I want to preserve. If someone takes the time to properly bluff his/her opponent and chooses a hard-counter fit for the match and steamrolls it, I think that is excellent, even if the match itself is not. :)<br><br>As always, all comments and suggestions are welcome.</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="331163748"><![CDATA[sign me up]]></row>
      <row messageID="331154454"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff"><br><br>--------------------------------<br>Cruiser Tournament Issues<br>From: </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1377//90192277">Gynax Gallenor</a><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Sent: 2013.09.26 01:22<br>To: Conquering Darkness, <br><br><br>Just a couple of points about the cruiser tournament.<br><br>First, applications for the tournament is open till the morning of Thursday, Oct 3. Prior to that, I will send out an evemail with all the applicants I have listed, probably on the Wednesday. Once the entrants are finalised, I will add them all to the website and do the brackets. The brackets will determine the matchups and the start time. I will schedule matches in 10 minute intervals, though I am not sure exactly what time we will start, as we will try to accomodate as many people as possible, so this really depends on the numbers.<br><br>Second, I implied this in the email, but just to be clear, just one toon per player, but like last time, you are free to change out your toon prior to the list being finalised next week. Once the brackets are up though, the toon you entered is the one you need to use.<br><br>Thirdly, since it is Double Elimination, the minimum ships you are likely to need is two. Like before, fits do not need to be declared prior to the match starting, so if you want to have a small stable of choices, that is perfectly fine.<br><br>Fourthly, all matches will take place in Caprica, so make sure you are in the wormhole, just in case Bob frowns on us that day.<br><br>Our plan is to make tournaments like this a monthly thing, and I am open to all sorts of ideas for tournaments, so feel free to get in touch with me if you have something you like the sound of.</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="331154442"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff"><br>Here ya go...<br><br>BTW, you need to have your ships in the hole this time. No runs to Amarr for a ship. :)<br><br>--------------------------------<br>1v1 Cruiser Tournament - Weekend of Oct 5/6<br>From: </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1377//90192277">Gynax Gallenor</a><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Sent: 2013.09.25 02:22<br>To: Conquering Darkness, <br><br><br>Sign up for the tournament is now open and is done by sending an evemail to Gynax. The format is very simple, in the subject line needs to be of the format<br><br>Subject: CRUISER TOURNAMENT - &lt;Entrant Toon Name&gt;<br><br>And just so I can call it in advance, any muppet who non-ironically puts that verbatim into the evemail is hereby being notified to prepare for public mocking. I know there is one of you out there. :)<br><br><br><br>Tournament Rules<br><br>(Note: In the following rules, the term 'happy panda' is short-hand for the obvious cocktail of 1 Pflepsen, 1 Archon, 10 max-damage sentry drones and 1 poor unfortunate. In deference to our members' imaginations, I will omit the fine details)<br><br><br>1. Each match consist of two contestants, who are flying in T1 cruisers of any race. Navy and Pirate cruisers are not allowed.<br><br>2. Fittings must be Tech 2 or less (Meta level 5). Only T1 rigs are allowed. Anything higher than that is illegal and the contestant will be Happy Panda'd.<br><br>3. The match arena will consist of sphere within 100km of the anchor for the tournament. The anchor will be announced in advance of the match, and will be responsible for enforcing the 'Edge of Glory'. The penalty is the Happy Panda.<br><br>4. One minute before the start of the match, contestants must warp to within 30km of the anchor, who will lock them. Contestants can warp in at any they choose, from any starting point they choose. Any contestants not ready with a ship will forfeit the match.<br><br>5. Each match will last until one of the contestants is destroyed. After five minutes, the arena size will shrink by 5km every 30 seconds, shrinking to 95km from the anchor once match time goes to 5:30, 90km at 6:00 and so on till one of the contestants is destroyed.<br><br>6. The tournament structure is Double Elimination, and the brackets will be determined randomly (apart from ZePenguin and Tandail in Round 1). A match schedule will be posted in advance, but there is the possibility of rearranging games if all parties involved can agree.<br><br>7. Two minutes prior to the match, each contestant must send their fitting to the match referee. This locks your choice of ship and fit for that match, and any deviation from this will result in forfeiture of the match upon arrival in the arena. In a shock twist, the penalty is the Happy Panda<br><br>8. A website for the tournament has been created, and can be viewed at the following URL:<br><br></font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><loc><a href="http://challonge.com/cd201310cruiser">http://challonge.com/cd201310cruise</loc>r</a><br><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Once I have everyone signed up, I will put the brackets up there.<br><br>9. Only the arena anchor, match referee and two contestants are allowed on grid for matches. A stream of the game will be set up, so on-grid observation is not required. It is confusing for the contestants to have so many people on grid. Happy Panda enforcement applies.<br><br>10. The following prizes will be awarded for the tournament (one prize per pilot):<br><br>-- Overall Winner: Navy battlecruiser hull of the winner's choice<br>-- Most Entertaining/Creative Fit (as determined by the Corp Directors): T1 Battlecruiser Hull<br>-- Best-placed Pilot to not use T2 modules of any kind: Set of Genolution Core Implants</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="331154341"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Give me a min, I'll send you the list of rules, there's a format I'd like the entry email to be in, just makes life easier.<br><br>--------------------------------<br>Cruiser Tournament - I'm in<br>From: </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1377//91744644">Catherine Kamensky</a><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Sent: 2013.09.29 20:21<br>To: </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1377//90192277">Gynax Gallenor</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">,  <br><br><br><br>--------------------------------<br>Cruiser Tournament Next Weekend (Oct 5/6)<br>From: </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1377//90192277">Gynax Gallenor</a><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Sent: 2013.09.29 18:24<br>To: Conquering Darkness, <br><br><br>Hey all,<br><br>Okay, first of, just a gentle reminder that entry for the Cruiser tournament closes at downtime, Thursday Oct 3, the schedule will be posted that evening. I only have two entries at the moment, so please don't procrastinate if you want to enter. Also, this is the way you enter it, just telling me on comms "Yeah I'm in" does NOT count. :)<br><br>Also, to our newer members, don't be shy in taking part, it is a lot of fun.<br><br>To enter, send an evemail to Gynax with the following format.<br><br>Subject: CRUISER TOURNAMENT -</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="331153308"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Just kidding, we're going out again.<br><br>Form in </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><loc><a href="showinfo:5//30000158">Olo</a></loc></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">, fleet forms at 2130 departs at 2200. (one hour from now)<br><br>Same fleet doctrine! Minmatar!<br><br>Cheers,<br>Jayne</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="331151753"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff"><br><br>--------------------------------<br>Cruiser Tournament Next Weekend (Oct 5/6)<br>From: </font><font size="12" color="#ffffa600"><a href="showinfo:1377//90192277">Gynax Gallenor</a><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Sent: 2013.09.29 18:24<br>To: Conquering Darkness, <br><br><br>Hey all,<br><br>Okay, first of, just a gentle reminder that entry for the Cruiser tournament closes at downtime, Thursday Oct 3, the schedule will be posted that evening. I only have two entries at the moment, so please don't procrastinate if you want to enter. Also, this is the way you enter it, just telling me on comms "Yeah I'm in" does NOT count. :)<br><br>Also, to our newer members, don't be shy in taking part, it is a lot of fun.<br><br>To enter, send an evemail to Gynax with the following format.<br><br>Subject: CRUISER TOURNAMENT -</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="331146753"><![CDATA[<br>Hey all,<br><br>Okay, first of, just a gentle reminder that entry for the Cruiser tournament closes at downtime, Thursday Oct 3, the schedule will be posted that evening. I only have two entries at the moment, so please don't procrastinate if you want to enter. Also, this is the way you enter it, just telling me on comms "Yeah I'm in" does NOT count. :)<br><br>Also, to our newer members, don't be shy in taking part, it is a lot of fun.<br><br>To enter, send an evemail to Gynax with the following format.<br><br>Subject: CRUISER TOURNAMENT -]]></row>
      <row messageID="331040336"><![CDATA[<font size="12" color="#bfffffff">Just a reminder to everyone that we are always going to have fitted ships on corp contract.<br><br>I believe currently there are 2 Enyos, 1 Sacrilege and 1 Deimos available, all of them in Pimebeka.<br><br>The cost of the fitted ships is roughly the Amarr buy price (or at least what the corp spent on the ships)<br><br></font><font size="12" color="#fff7931e"><a href="contract:30001669//72708737">[Multiple Items] (Enyo)</a></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff"> <br><br></font><font size="12" color="#fff7931e"><a href="contract:30001669//72708750">[Multiple Items] (Enyo)</a><br><br><a href="contract:30001669//72798310">[Multiple Items] (Deimos)</a><a href="contract:30001669//72708750"> </a><br><br><a href="contract:30001669//72798645">[Multiple Items] (Sacrilege)</a><a href="contract:30001669//72708750"> </a><br><br></font><font size="12" color="#bfffffff">If these ships expire, I will just relist them. Our plan is to make sure line ships from our doctrines will always be available on corp contract.</font>]]></row>
      <row messageID="331035406"><![CDATA[Go with that Deimos fit. There should be one available in Pimebeka on corp contract. I think it is 180 million with fittings.<br><br>We also have the Sacrilege fit up on corp contract as well.]]></row>
      <row messageID="331007463"><![CDATA[Do you by any chance have any details on sites that have been ran since we moved into Caprica? And also the number of ship losses we have suffered?<br><br>By strange coincidence, I'm helping a guy tomorrow with a RL insurance issue, and I was planning to quickly ask him the best way to go about it, I have a few ideas, and can probably start working out some details in the next few days, but data always makes it better.<br><br>One thing that helps a lot is that it is just going to be a fixed period of time, so it is really just a fairly simple probability calculation, which helps. Data will improve this a lot though.<br><br>Were you thinking of having the fund purely for sites? Or also for PvP ops as well (cos while awesome - that could break the corp wallet if something went bad)?]]></row>
      <row messageID="331007000"><![CDATA[I actually had a completely different idea for a tournament at some point, just haven't worked out the details.<br><br>My idea is called "Stop the Gynax" (like the old cartoon) and my basic plan is that starting from Caprica in a covops, I have to get to somewhere in New Eden, and everyone else has to stop me, by podding me. And we only have one winner too, so that allows for some treachery too. :)<br><br>I haven't figured out exactly how we do this in a way that would be fun, but my thoughts were that I can use a jump clone if I want, I'm not restricted in terms of wormholes, and I can even engage in treachery - bribing someone to shoot the others letting me slip past in the confusion, all that sort of thing.<br><br>I would need a few details to make it challenging for both sides and not just a case of everyone camping on a gate (though when that does inevitably happen that would be a good time for a bit of old-fashioned bribery like I said).<br><br>Anyway, it is something totally different, and could be a lot of fun, though to get the numbers required we might need to invite Sativa to get the critical mass, which I know is something you have been thinking about too.<br><br>I like the idea if I can think about setting it up properly, not sure what the prize could be yet either.<br><br>Do you think the idea has merit?]]></row>
    </rowset>
  </result>
  <cachedUntil>2023-09-30 11:05:24</cachedUntil>
</eveapi>