<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<eveapi version="2">
  <currentTime>2013-10-02 11:05:30</currentTime>
  <result>
    <rowset name="messages" key="messageID" columns="messageID">
      <row messageID="311646124"><![CDATA[Hello space friends!<br><br>My name is Lyris Chronicles of Narnia in the World of Tomorrow's Goonfleet dot Com, whom you may remember from the forums dot EVE Online as the Spacebook Superstar and Sky Captain of Your Heart. I am here to speak to you today about the Council of Stellar Management, and of the fine men and women empowered by You, the People, to sit on that gestalt panel.<br><br>I am a newcomer to the political arena, and those of you who read the forums may have noticed that my activity has suffered a sharp decline over the past week which coincided with the opening of the polls. This was not unintentional. Looking at the numbers and addressing them with all the honour and humility which has thus far supported my campaign, I cannot in good conscience go forward at this time. To do so would be to speak against my stated ideals; to do so would be to dilute the voting power of the public; to do so would be to be dishonest to both myself and to my constituency; to do so would be a waste of Your time, and of mine. It is for this reason, that I have no realistic chance of securing one of the winning seats, that I am announcing my unconditional surrender to and offering my endorsement of Alexander Gianturco, AKA The Mittani, AKA The King of Space, AKA the CEO and Executor of the GoonWaffe corporation of the Right Honourable GoonSwarm Federation (of Space Planets) alliance, the same being the First Among Equals in the Clusterfuck Coalition of Very Good Space Friends (in space).<br><br>This is a man whom has experience both in game and in his real life occupation as a corporate attorney in dealing with people, with politics, and with policies which affect more than just himself. He is by his nature as a legal advocate accustomed to the role of serving, exactly as I had promised to serve my own constituency if elected, the interests of not himself but of the charges under his ward; in short, my friends, he is a man who will fight for Your honour and for the honour of this great institution we call Democracy.<br><br>I invite you all to go to the polls, and to vote for The Mittani so that he may continue to serve as Chairman of the Council.<br><br>Do it for Democracy.<br>Do it for Friendship.<br><br>http://community.eveonline.com/council/voting/Vote.asp?c=438<br>]]></row>
    </rowset>
  </result>
  <cachedUntil>2023-09-30 11:05:30</cachedUntil>
</eveapi>